Done?
I am running a maintenance patch.
All the CCTV cameras will
be offline for ten minutes.
Salaam alaikum, Mr. Ansari.
Seems like it's God's will…
that London's air suits you.
Tell your men to back down.
I have just come by…
to say hello.
Major Sameer!
They let you out of prison!
Congrats!
Listen, Sameer.
I know what you're thinking.
Believe me, there was no other way.
I am sorry.
Is that all the faith you had in me?
General!
If Mission Zulfiqar had succeeded--
Yes, but it didn't, Sameer.
I heard you had a Plan B in place,
which succeeded?
Why, Sameer?
You bought into the stories…
we tell our recruits?
What did you achieve with Plan B?
Absolutely nothing.
Plan A was superior.
A nerve gas attack…
could have triggered a war.
But that did not happen.
Because you betrayed us.
Plan B was also meant
to be smaller in scale.
And by the grace of Allah,
it was a success.
It's unfortunate that
the Indian government
projected it as an accident
and changed the narrative.
General!
If you hadn't betrayed us for this
sacrilegious life in London,
things would have been so different today.
I had no other option, Sameer.
The Prime Minister had already
cut a deal with the Indians.
What would you have done
had you been in my place?
There's no point in clinging
to the past, Mr. Ansari.
Let us look at the future.
I have a new plan.
Zulfiqar 2.0.
I may need your help.
Of course!
Do call me, whenever you need anything.
God willing!
Goodbye, Mr. Ansari.
What happened? Help him!
Oh, my God!
We need to make the delivery to
the customer in a couple of days.
Are we on track, Raji?
I think, something is stuck here.
What soap do you use?
You smell really good.
Raji, you don't wear
your hair up these days.
It is about safety.
I don't want your hair to get
caught in the machine, you know.
It isn't a rule or anything.
I am just looking out for you, that's all.
Nanda!
-Hello, Mr. Kothari!
-I was looking for you.
-Can we meet now?
-Yes, I'll come.
Raji…
you look really good when you
tie your hair up in a bun.
Get down fast if this is your stop.
Hurry up and please, make way!
"Your present circumstances
don't determine where you can go.
They merely determine where you start."
Dad, what does this mean?
Your present…
circumstances don't determine…
where you can go.
They merely determine…
where you start.
Even I can do this 50-50 translation.
Why did you bring him along?
He had so many classes.
I didn't get a chance to drop him home.
How's Arvind doing?
I don't know.
Must be fine.
Aren't you guys in touch?
Suchi!
What is the need to bring in a third
person to solve problems in our marriage?
This isn't a goddamn disease!
Yes, sir?
We can sort this out ourselves.
Do you want to add anything to this?
Me?
Excuse me?
-Have you filled the form?
-Don't need this.
Yes.
Sir, may I have the form?
Sir, we give this book to all the couples.
Only to those who need it, I am sure?
No, sir. We give it to everyone.
Sir, you get a free relaxation
audio file with the book.
The doctor recommends you read
this book before your next appointment.
Is it free?
It's complimentary…
with a 25% discount.
Complimentary or discounted?
So, Suchitra…
you didn't want your husband to be
working in a dangerous environment.
You wanted him to do a conventional job.
But as soon as Srikant found himself
a corporate job, you quit your job.
That's because I wanted to
spend more time with the kids.
And you, Srikant.
Switching jobs…
must have been tough.
Any trouble adapting to your new life?
Not really.
I adapt very quickly. I am alright.
For the time being,
let us set this discussion aside.
Let us do a simple exercise, okay?
Srikant…
tell me five things…
you are grateful to Suchitra for.
Five things?
I-I mean, why only five?
There are many things which
I really admire about her.
I mean…
like, I am really grateful that…
she never lets the kids feel
my absence in their lives.
And…
and…
she's a very good Bharatanatyam dancer.
She excels at it.
And sambar… she cooks it so well!
And rasam!
Yeah!
Even if you count sambar and rasam,
that's only four things, Sri.
He put me on the spot.
You should've warned me about this
quiz show. I would have come prepared.
Okay, Srikant! Relax!
Now, your turn.
He's a great dad.
He's a very principled man.
Great sense of humor.
Very intelligent.
He's very committed and hardworking.
And…
he can cook up a lie at the drop of a hat.
Okay, now.
How physically intimate
are you with each other?
As in…
-how often--
-How often what?
I mean to ask how physically
intimate you are in life.
Generally, you know.
Are you asking…
how many times we have sex?
Physical intimacy is just not about sex.
It's much more.
It's an indicator of your emotional bond.
Holding hands.
A hug or a kiss before leaving for work.
Cuddling.
These are…
quite personal details!
Srikant, stop looking
at sex as a taboo subject.
You should be able
to talk openly about it.
Is this a joke?
This is so childish!
I'll get better advice than this
from a simple search on my phone.
Mr. Srikant, you can become
knowledgeable from others' knowledge.
But you cannot become
wise from others' wisdom.
You can find this quote on Google!
I never said it was my quote.
Even I know a few quotes.
"If you and I agree on everything,
then one of us is unnecessary,
-for fuck's sake."
-Keep quiet.
"Sometimes, to win, you must lose first,
and he who wins after losing
is called the Gambler."
-What?
-"Beyond fear lies victory."
"To the victor go the spoils."
"Motherfucker!"
-Suchitra, what is this?
-He's a doctor!
-We are paying for these quotes?
-This is a therapy session!
Fuck it! I am not part of it!
-I am not part of it!
-Srikant!
He's a fraud!
Let us go, Atharv.
He needs serious help.
I promise I'll get another appointment.
Really sorry.
Charge them 3,000.
Actually, wait.
Charge them 5,000.
And they pay for the book.
That's right.
It's safe.
There are no cameras installed here.
You will run this entire operation, Sajid.
I've been waiting to go back to India.
You're going there for
a really honorable mission.
I want your 100% focus on this mission.
We have the opportunity
to attack India once again.
-Let us not waste--
-Brother Sameer, I will do my job.
Stay under the radar.
Complete the mission.
And get out!
No personal work.
Yes.
And don't do anything…
that I wouldn't approve of.
Passport and ticket.
Your flight leaves in six hours.
God be with you.
Goodbye.
Hello?
Hello, Mr. Sambit.
I am Deepan from London.
I hope you remember me.
Oh! Hi, Deepan.
I think, you have…
Subbu in your custody.
He's the Foreign Minister
of our government.
Government in Exile.
You technically are not a government.
No, no, no!
Even the UK and France are close
to offering us support at this time.
What do you want from me, Deepan?
We want Subbu back.
He killed Indian officers.
He has to go through the due process
according to the law of the land.
Are you going to gift
Subbu to the Lankans?
That's ridiculous.
I am sure we can work something out.
You are not bound by international laws.
Please!
Don't hand him over to the Lankans.
I'll see what I can do, Deepan.
I can't promise you anything.
Mr. Sambit,
I'd like to tell you one thing.
If something happens to Subbu…
there will be repercussions,
and it'll be beyond my control.
Are you threatening me?
No, no, no.
I am not threatening you.
I am just asking for your help.
I don't want my movement
to be derailed again.
Like I said…
I'll see whatever I can do.
But you must tell Bhaskaran…
that his brother crossed
the limits this time.
And Deepan, keep your movement
in mind before you do anything.
You don't want to put us in a position
where we have to extend
the ban on your organization indefinitely.
You don't want to do that…
right?
Bhaskaran.
Bad news?
I wish I could say no.
India will use Subbu to score
brownie points with Sri Lanka.
Not necessarily. I spoke to Sambit.
Let us wait and see.
If I were the man I was ten years ago--
The Government of France…
is about to lift the ban on us.
We need to be coolheaded about this.
What do you want me to do?
The Lankans will kill Subbu for sure.
We could have done something
if only Subbu had not tried to escape.
You are the one who sent him to India.
We!
We sent him!
Deepan!
I don't care what you do.
I want Subbu back in London.
Hi!
Since when have you been waiting here?
About an hour.
You are mad!
About you?
Yes!
Now don't do this stupid, filmy shit.
How was school?
Don't ask.
Hey, dude!
Aren't you going home?
If Mom calls, just tell her
I am studying with you,
and can't talk because I am in the loo.
Kalyan, Mahima. Mahima, Kalyan.
Hi.
Where are you taking me?
It's a surprise.
What are we doing here?
Seriously, where are we going?
Come.
Trust me.
Okay, Dhriti!
Close your eyes.
What?
You said you trust me…
right?
Close your eyes.
Okay.
Great!
Come.
Left.
-Where?
-Take it easy.
Kalyan, I am really scared, okay?
Don't be scared.
I'll open?
Wait.
-What the fuck!
-Calm down!
-Let me go, please!
-Don't worry. Nothing's going to happen.
I am not gonna let you fall.
Just open your eyes…
and see the view.
This is a view?
Are you new in Mumbai?
Okay, my bad.
Have you ever broken a rule?
Yes.
Yeah? When?
When I…
I don't think so.
Honestly, I don't think
you've ever broken a rule.
You need to be home before dark.
You don't talk to too many boys.
You've obviously never had boyfriends.
How do you know I've
never had a boyfriend?
Well, I can guess that much.
Really?
Really.
Who is it?
Mom. I have to go.
Okay, later.
I will count to ten…
and you will fall asleep.
One.
Two.
-Three.
-Stop playing with my chain!
It will break.
Nobody ever wants to play with me.
Please play with me.
Okay, fine.
-What do I have to do?
-Just lean back a little.
Lean back.
Close your eyes.
Now, you are totally relaxed.
And you are going to do exactly as I say.
This is a really dumb game.
Get lost!
It's all about visualization.
Think about the first
time you touched her.
You stroked her hair.
Papa!
Think of that.
What do you want?
Please play with me.
Playtime is over.
Finish your homework, and go to sleep.
Nobody cares about my future.
Visualize the life entering
your body from the light.
Kattappa!
Before I count to ten…
you will fall asleep!
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Kattappa fell asleep!
Did you see that?
What?
Kattappa fell asleep!
I didn't see it.
Shit! Did anyone else see that?
No one saw?
You know, I've finished half of that book.
It's really very good.
Very nice.
Good.
JK!
Let's meet in the evening?
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday!
Srikant…
follow me.
You know what? I am 28, right?
And I am the CEO.
How did that happen?
How?
Because I never think small, you know?
I am a team player!
I…
always think about me…
my team…
my company…
my country.
You know?
What more can I do for my country!
For my company!
Not now! Later.
Okay, let us take her for example.
I don't even know her name.
But I will make sure…
that I am present at her
cake-cutting ceremony.
You on the other hand, I…
I never see you at any…
any team-building exercises. Any…
cake-cutting sessions.
Any other activities in the office.
If that is the case, you know, I'll…
I'll enroll myself in
an upcoming workshop, and…
I'll sing at every birthday party…
-"Happy birthday to you!"
-It's not about that, man.
I'll show you something.
Yes!
Read this.
Read what your colleagues,
your younger colleagues
have to say about you.
Go on.
"He belongs in a government office."
"Working with him is like having your…
dad…
as your classmate in college."
"He needs to…
G-A-L."
-What is--
-Get a life, Srikant!
Get a life, man!
We'll do your review,
the next review, after three months.
You know, I give you three months!
And don't forget…
the five golden words motto.
You do know that, right?
Yes, that's the "minimum guy" thing.
"Don't be a minimum guy."
Yeah.
Repeat after me.
Don't…
be a minimum guy!
Hey, come on!
It's good for your heart! Do it!
Don't be a minimum guy!
-Don't be a minimum guy!
-Minimum guy.
That's good, my boy!
Do it!
Fuck this shit.
Hello, sir!
My name is Unmesh Joshi.
I am a journalist at Navbharat Jyot.
How can I help you?
Sir, a year ago,
this video of a Kashmiri student,
Kareem Bhatt, had leaked online.
He had claimed that our…
security agencies were trying to kill him.
I don't have any idea
what you're talking about.
Sir! The video was leaked on the internet,
and vanished mysteriously
after a few hours.
Look, what did you say your name was?
-Unmesh Joshi.
-Right, Mr. Joshi,
I work here at this IT firm.
There's been a misunderstanding.
-Now, if you'll excuse me…
-Mr. Srikant Tiwari.
I know that you worked for
the NIA's special unit, TASC.
Sir, I've tried to ask a lot of people,
but nobody wants to talk about it.
I thought, since you've already quit TASC,
maybe, you could tell me something.
Mr. Srikant!
Why did you quit your job at TASC?
Did you quit TASC because
of Kareem Bhatt's death?
I am the press! You can't touch me!
I have no statement to give to you.
For your own sake, stay away from me.
If I see you near me again, I'll bloody--
I am not going to let you get
away with it, Srikant Tiwari!
-Hi, Auntie! How are you?
-Hi, I am doing alright.
Zoya, look who it is!
Hey, Milind!
-Go, see her. I'll get you some tea.
-Yes.
-Sit, sit, sit.
-I am fine, I am fine, I am fine.
-Good to see you.
-How are you?
I just get dizzy…
a little bit, that's it.
-For you.
-Thank you.
Better?
Can I bum a cigarette?
-Have you lost your mind?
-Just give me one, quick!
Mom will be here soon
with the tea. Please!
Why are you doing this?
Take this pack from me later.
So, to what do I owe this surprise?
Mr. Srikant and JK had stopped by.
TASC wants you back?
What did you say?
I haven't made up my mind yet.
If nothing had happened to me…
what would you have said to them?
Milind, I am fine.
I am fine.
Whatever happened, it wasn't your fault.
Don't punish yourself.
-But Zoya, I just--
-Milind, just…
promise me that…
you'll come back safe, okay?
Promise?
Now, go have a chat with my mother.
And keep her distracted.
I need to smoke this in peace.
Otherwise, she'll shout at me again.
-Auntie, do you need any help?
-No, I am fine. Sugar?
Half a teaspoon.
I hope she didn't ask you for a cigarette.
No, she didn't.
Do stop by whenever you can.
It cheers her up.
Sri!
Who was this journalist?
Unmesh Joshi, sir.
I don't think you need
to worry about this video.
I think it was barely online for an hour,
following which we had it taken down.
If these people try…
to contact you again…
or if they in any way try to…
be in touch with you,
please, make no contact with them.
Look, we'll take care of it.
Sir…
I am just lost.
This guilt is really eating me up.
Everybody wants the truth
to be on their side.
Yet, nobody wants to stand by the truth.
Just think about Kareem's family.
They'll all have to spend the remainder
of their lives with the guilt…
thinking their son was a terrorist.
They deserve to know the truth.
Unfortunately…
that is the price for peace.
It's the way it is, Sri.
You aren't in this alone.
Everyone is guilty.
All of us!
We would reach the court in a couple
of minutes. Inform the judge. Over.
Copy, sir. Our pilot vehicle
has reached the court.
They said the judge will be there
by the time you reach. Over.
The Traffic DC has agreed
to the green channel, sir.
Okay!
Secure the perimeter!
And clear everyone from the area.
Clear, clear, clear!
Bring him.
Clear there.
In the southern Indian city of Chennai,
the opposition leaders have blamed
the administration and Ms. Basu
for the death of Mr. Subramaniam
Palanivel also known as Subbu.
The administration, however,
categorically dismissed
the allegations as baseless.
Many casualties were feared after
an explosion in a Chennai court.
The police are not ruling out that
this could be a terrorist attack.
-Down with police brutality!
The ISI is involved in Subbu's death?
-We have a report with credible intel--
-This whole thing has become a joke!
We can't pin every
problem we face on the ISI!
Martyr Subbu!
Tamil Eelam deserves justice!
Martyrs never die, Chief.
We should start a campaign
on social media, #JusticeforSubbu.
I spoke to our supporters in Chennai,
even they are not able to wrap
their head around this.
No, no! I spoke to the French Government.
I hope this will not hinder the process.
Chief!
Ravi!
What happened?
-I can't do this anymore.
-What rubbish!
I don't have the strength
to fight anymore.
I quit the government.
Until the next council elections,
you be the PM.
Do you even understand what you're saying?
Bhaskaran, we need you!
No… you don't.
The world has changed.
There is no place for
soldiers like me in it.
I want to spend the rest of my days alone.
Congratulations, Prime Minister!
It's not a secret.
PM Basu hates our people!
I think, PM Basu did this to please
her old friend Rupatunga.
I don't understand why these
people hate me so much.
I've done so much for them.
Sambit!
Call Rupatunga's office right away.
Fix a date for bilateral talks.
To be held in Chennai.
Ma'am, Chennai--
-Ma'am, I think--
-Just do as I say!
Rupatunga will think that…
we are behind Subbu's death.
Let him think like that.
I am sorry for your loss.
Sorry about your brother.
That Basu!
She always hated us!
In the past too…
she helped kill our movement.
Now, she killed my brother.
He was the only family I had.
Bastards!
Brother!
I am with you…
in this war.
Whatever help you need…
just let me know.
Thank you, Sameer.
I want to make Basu pay for this.
Fuck!
I'll recover all the money I lost.
Motherfucking bastards!
Deal the cards. I'll be back.
-Hello?
-Selva, how are you?
Chief!
I heard about Brother Subbu.
I can't bear it!
Selva, are you drunk?
No, no, Chief.
Clean up!
I'll call you back in a few minutes.
You told us that we are
not giving up on the war.
It has been a long wait, Chief.
I am itching to go back to war!
Can you stay sober, Selva?
Yes, of course, I can.
I expect my soldiers
to be completely focused.
I am sorry, Chief.
The alcohol numbed the pain,
but it never made me forget.
But now, I've realized that only
war can heal the wounds of war.
Selva, stop it!
Melodrama is for losers.
Put together a small team.
Who's left from before?
-We are four of us.
-Alright.
One more thing,
I am sending someone to help you.
What for? We are enough.
Don't ever question my wisdom, Selva.
We are not what we used to be.
We need help.
I need you to cooperate with him.
When do we start?
Now!
Have you bought your ticket?
Show me your ticket.
Hey!
Why do you need to stick
to that girl and stand?
Tie a saree to a bamboo pole and these
idiots will be all over it! Dogs!
Hey, shut up and get back in here!
Take this seat!
Following the death of
Subramaniam Palanivel…
the leader of
the Tamil Government in Exile,
Bhaskaran, has quit the movement.
The future of their decades-long
freedom struggle is uncertain.
Is this the end?
One day, our shoulders will be free
From the burden of all the sorrows
Motherland, goodbye!
Raji?
Brother Selva!
How are you, Raji?
Getting by. I'd be lying if I told you
I hadn't thought of killing myself.
The movement decides what you
do with your life, remember?
I saw the news about Subbu's death.
Are they hunting us down now?
I got a call from Chief.
What did he say?
-Subbu's death must have--
-I hope things are going fine for you.
Ever had any trouble?
Any run-in with the cops?
No.
No, nothing.
Everything is fine.
Why, brother?
Quit your job…
and wait for the instructions.
Okay, brother.
You know what this means, Raji?
We have a mission.
I don't have to remind you…
martyrs never die.
Ready for the mission, Raji?
"I am the weapon my
motherland gave birth to!
I will fight for my cause!
I will protect our Tamil race!
I will lay down my
life for our motherland!"