Sir!
What is this, man?
Look at this news, Deepan.
What's new? This is old news.
These idiots have killed me so many times.
Where's Subbu?
He is near the tents.
-I hope we are ready for the operation.
-Yes.
We are waiting for some
more weapons to arrive.
We have no time, guys! Step on it!
Focus on the job.
Subbu and his team seem
well-prepared, as always.
Yes, that goes inside. Yes, just like
that. All right? Everything is set now.
And from tomorrow,
you will be our leader's shadow.
-Understood?
-Subbu!
Check this out.
They are messing with us.
Brother, three more days.
After we hit Rupatunga, the world
will know who is dead and who is alive.
Let us review the plan.
Sir!
We hit their forward bases,
about 11 km from here.
If all goes well, we will regain
control of the highways.
Next, our cells in Colombo will hit
the parliament, airports, and the harbor.
-Nice plan.
-Good job.
Brother, Selva is setting up
the 12.7 mm machine gun.
Please, take a look at it.
Bhaskaran!
Even after all these years of fighting…
Subbu is excited about every
battle like it is his first.
He just loves war!
-My brother loves freedom, not war.
-Selva!
Hurry up! It'll be dark soon!
Yes.
Selva… have you tested
the grenade launcher?
I'll test it today.
Hey, finish it right now!
Understood?
We can't afford to fail this time.
What are you thinking about?
-We have to strike as planned.
-Nothing.
I was hoping that Rupatunga
would agree for peace talks.
Idiot Rupatunga!
If we want to end this war…
then Rupatunga is our only hope.
He will offer us the same shit again.
Autonomy.
What we want is freedom.
Wonder when you'll ditch those bastards.
Stop talking politics, and start fighting.
Back straight! Chin up!
-That's right!
-Subbu!
A dead soldier is no good.
Don't preach to me about death.
We not only lost our families…
but also witnessed the loot,
murder, and rapes of countless innocents.
You stick to politics
and eloquent speeches, Deepan.
Leave the war to us soldiers.
Even I lost my family, Subbu.
Without eloquent speeches
and politics, this war will never end.
Calm down, brother!
We wouldn't be here
without Deepan's hard work.
Okay, all right.
Everyone, help yourselves.
It will be a few days
before your next hot meal.
Ilango, is everything ready?
Everyone must be tired and hungry.
Call everyone to eat!
Everyone, come eat!
Hurry up, everyone! Let's eat!
Selva! Tell them to hurry up!
-Sir!
-Did we get Bhaskaran?
Neither Bhaskaran, Deepan, or Subbu.
All three got away.
We can't let them get away again!
Understood?
Yes, sir!
We can't just run away like this.
If we die,
so does our decades-long movement.
There is no other way!
What do we do now?
We are leaving our homeland?
We can't stay here anymore.
We will save the movement
at the right time.
Brother!
What is this madness?
We are leaving our homeland?
The future of our struggle
rests on our shoulders!
The three of us need to survive.
For the sake of our dead family,
the thousands of innocents that died…
don't you think I will continue the fight?
Our time will come.
Find out where they are headed.
Minister Basu has assured me she wouldn't
allow any rebels to get into India.
Did the Indians respond
to our distress messages?
I have been trying to contact
them for the past 48 hours.
We did not get any response from them.
They said they will help,
but they abandoned us!
We are in this situation
because we trusted Basu!
Backstabbers!
But guess who did respond?
I have spoken to Local 52. He has a ship
waiting for us in international waters.
They destroyed our
people, raped our women,
and mercilessly murdered our children.
They will pay.
Hi!
Good morning.
What's the time, Srikant?
It's 9:20 a.m.
So, you're late, right?
The company policy says I can come in
anytime between 9:00 and 9:30, right?
But you could show up
at nine o'clock, couldn't you?
Well, I could even show up at 8:30 a.m.
Do you know how much money
Mukesh Ambani makes per minute?
Guess.
Ten… maybe, fifteen thousand?
He makes over a crore per minute.
That means,
he makes around two lakhs per second.
You know, if he drops a 2,000-rupee note,
he doesn't bother to pick it up.
He doesn't even touch it! Do you know why?
Because he'll lose two lakh rupees!
That's what I am talking about!
Every second counts, Srikant.
In this new world,
it's not enough to do the bare minimum.
You don't want to be that
"minimum guy," do you?
Good! I aim for perfection,
and I'll settle for excellence.
Yes. In my conference room, right now!
It's the same bullshit every day.
That little weasel is going to teach
me the importance of time?
All talk and no cock.
And what the hell is a "minimum guy"?
Sure, go ahead and laugh,
but this is all because of you.
All because of me?
You hounded me every day,
"Corporate world! Corporate world!
Nine to five! Nine to five!"
Do you know how many people
want a job here at Cache Me?
Tanmay is a young achiever. Maybe,
you can learn a few things from him.
This is a new world!
New world? What the hell has changed?
Same government!
Same war! Same terrorists!
Pakistan is now under
an ultra right-wing regime!
And now, ISI is back to--
Sri, saving the world
is not your job anymore.
Forget Pakistan and ISI!
And maybe, start thinking
about your TPS reports!
Mr. Rupatunga, you keep saying
India is Sri Lanka's elder sister…
and you do this?
I guess, the Chinese are
your best friends now?
Hope your welcome party for
the Chinese Premier went very well?
Ms. Basu, after all these years,
you haven't changed a bit.
The Chinese Premier's
visit was just a formality.
I hear that you are planning to give…
the North Sri Lanka port
construction deal to the Chinese?
The Chinese want it, yes.
But we still haven't decided on
it, Ms. Basu.
We cannot let the Chinese
control our Indian Ocean.
It's between us.
Well, the Chinese
are making a great offer.
We are a small and developing
nation, and we need all the help.
Mr. Rupatunga,
you have forgotten our help…
when you were struggling
to solve the rebel problem?
What do you have in mind?
We are willing to extend a very
low-interest long-term loan.
We'll build a port, train your
people, and hand it over.
No strings attached.
Let me think about it.
Mr. Rupatunga,
there is something else in your mind.
What is it?
I need a small thing, Ms. Basu.
A wanted man in our country
is in India at this moment.
Bhaskaran's brother…
Subbu Subramaniam Palanivel
is in Chennai right now…
to rally the support of some MLAs and MPs.
You know it very well, that this
organization is already banned in India.
I got some information
that France is considering
recognizing this government.
Can you believe that?
These people want to form a government
and operate from London.
-If you could give Subbu to us--
-But Subbu is not a wanted man in India.
Arresting him will be a big problem
in India! Especially in Tamil Nadu!
Mr. Rupatunga, what else can I do for you?
Ms. Basu, we know we are a very small
nation, but please, allow us our pride.
If France and the UK
recognize this government,
then, not too far away, very soon…
they will sit with us at the UN,
and I cannot…
I cannot allow that.
I will see what I can do.
That's all I ask, Ms. Basu.
I'll wait for your call.
Hey, Tiwari!
Hey!
-How have you been?
-You're looking smart!
-Have a seat!
-I hope you aren't having an affair!
You've lost your mind! Just sit down.
Here you go, it's my treat.
So, order yourself a feast.
I could buy my whole vada
pav stall for these prices.
-Excuse me, one Caesar salad.
-From vada pav to salads!
And one portion of garlic bread.
-And one fresh lime soda.
-Okay.
What about you, sir?
I'll have pasta.
Sure, sir. Which one?
-Agg… leeyo… olio?
-Aglio olio, sir.
Anything to drink, sir?
-Two hundred fifty bucks for a Coke?
-Just order what you like.
I'd rather die than pay
that much for a Coke.
You just bring me that pasta.
I'll have a cold drink somewhere else.
For now, get me water.
Still or sparkling, sir?
Just regular water?
Yes, sir. Okay. Be there shortly.
What the hell is this?
I hope they know this
restaurant is in India.
Why does that dish have such a weird name?
So, how's it going?
The economy is in deep shit.
They cut our Diwali bonus by half.
-Seriously?
-Yeah.
You guys are going to be really busy soon.
A hard-line party is coming
to power in Pakistan.
Kulkarni has had a bunch of
high-level meetings about this.
Sharma has briefed us about this, too.
You always know what's going
on, don't you?
You don't really mean it when you
say you love your IT job, do you?
Your heart is still very much at TASC.
-I am very happy! Very happy!
-I don't believe you!
I don't want the burden
of people's lives or deaths on me.
If only we'd reached
Orion Chemicals faster.
Stop blaming yourself.
It wasn't your fault, so why do you--
Leave all that!
How's Suchi?
I don't understand, Talpade.
I reach home on time.
I spend time with the kids.
I cook breakfast in the morning,
and I cook dinner at night.
Still, Suchi just isn't happy.
Every time I ask her, she just says,
"Oh, I am fine! Nothing's wrong!"
Do yourself a favor, Tiwari.
Come back to TASC.
We will tolerate you
no matter how boring you are.
Suchi must just be fed up with you by now!
-Excuse me, where's my order?
-Sir, it'll be here shortly.
Thank you.
Mr. Srikant, may I have a word
with you if you don't mind?
What has Dhriti done now?
-I hope you haven't messed up!
-I haven't! Promise!
-Good evening, ma'am!
-Good evening.
All well? Any problem at school?
-Or the compound? Or anything else?
-All good, all good. Thank you.
I just want to have
a quick word about Atharv.
-Atharv?
-Yes!
He's been very hyperactive.
He keeps playing this shooting video game,
and he's very hard to handle.
In his generation,
half the kids have ADHD.
A--AD?
Attention Deficit Hyperactivity
Disorder, Mr. Srikant.
And we don't want Atharv to have
any problems now, do we?
Please, stop buying him
these expensive gifts!
No, no. Those are not
expensive gifts, ma'am.
He has an Apple Watch now, I believe.
No, no. It's just a Chinese replica!
Don't tell him, please.
You see, at their age, they have a lot
of energy, and nowhere to channel it.
To channelize precisely that,
we put him in music classes.
He has been learning for two years now.
So, I am sure he'll be
able to channel his energy!
That music class!
You see, I always encourage the children…
-to pursue whatever they like,
-Yeah.
and not really worry about the results.
But in Atharv's case…
You understand what I mean, Mr. Srikant.
Pa, pick any song in the world.
I can play anything now!
Do you intend to torture me
with that all the way home?
Papa, please! Name a song!
"Sare jahan se achha."
What kind of a song is that?
Name a song from a movie.
From a movie?
Alright, then.
O, darling! O, darling!
Flowers are blooming--
What song is this?
Don't ask anyone else that,
unless you want to be humiliated!
It's a song from a classic film
called, "Sholay."
I am going to play "Senorita" for you.
Don't blow so hard,
it'll come out of your rear end.
It's hot! Please, use a coaster.
Hello! Dhriti! Why are you late?
Didn't your tuition
class get over two hours ago?
-Boyfriend?
-Shut up!
I was at Mahima's house, studying.
We have a test coming up.
All right, come to have dinner.
-Hey, Suchi!
-Yes?
Should we go watch a film this Saturday?
Yes, yes!
Let's decide on Saturday?
I need a new laptop.
Now, don't tell me you have all your money
stuck in the new house you've bought!
Oh, come on! Come on!
Just because he is a boy,
he gets everything.
And because I am a girl,
all I get are excuses.
This is the problem with our patriarchal
society, with its deep-rooted misogyny.
Suchi… did you hear her?
How good is her English!
Such command over the language!
She writes an essay even for
"True or False" questions these days.
-Shut up!
-You shut up!
All right! That's enough! Peace.
-Come on, give me your phone.
-Just one more game!
Nope! No more phones during dinner, okay?
A family that eats together…
stays together, okay?
Healthy families follow this rule.
-And what if I have a special class?
-And what if I had a special camp?
-And I have to study late and get up late?
-And if I had a fever, what then?
And what if I had piles!
What?
Why the hell do you always
have to focus on the exception?
Unless there is a catastrophic
earthquake that kills us all…
I am sure we can have dinner together!
-Atharv, no more phones. Family time!
-Papa, I just have one level left, please?
-It's a family rule.
-Please?
-Family time.
-Family time, goddammit!
-Srikant!
Sorry.
How was your day?
Come on, guys!
One by one, we'll all share something.
Like, "How was your day,
and what all did you do today?"
Dhriti, how was your day?
There's nothing to tell, Pa.
I went to school.
I attended classes and then, I came home.
That's it? That's all you did today?
Okay, I have exciting news for you guys.
Today, our broker sent me the
first photograph of our new house.
-Show! Show it to us!
-Okay, calm down! I am showing it.
Okay, I am breaking the phone rule,
because this is very exciting.
-This--
-That's our building?
No, no. That's not our building.
That's Tower A.
You see this space here? That's Tower C.
It's upcoming. That's where we'll live.
The foundation has been laid out, and
very soon, they'll build the ten floors.
What?
Be patient. Everything will work out.
So, Suchi, tell us.
What did you do? How was your day?
Well, I didn't do much. I watched some TV.
-Then, I cooked.
-Okay.
Then, I watched TV all over again.
And tomorrow, I have an exciting
day of watching television and…
doing absolutely nothing.
Why aren't you ever in
a good mood anymore?
Sometimes, I think,
you just don't like my face!
I was trying to spend some
quality time with the family.
-And you just keep--
-Sri! Just stop stretching it now!
Why don't you leave it?
Don't make a mountain out of a molehill!
I am stretching it?
Suchi, everything is
not an argument, okay?
Sometimes, I feel, a fight breaks
out even before I open my mouth.
Sri…
I am sorry.
I didn't mean it like that.
Actually…
it's not your fault.
I…
I have been seeing a counselor
for a few days now.
I know you don't like these things, but…
would you be willing to come
to see the counselor with me?
I think it'll be good.
Tiwari. It's Puneet.
-Yes, Puneet.
-Sir.
Vaibhav Therani's phone just came online.
Maybe, it just got a signal.
He's at Orion Chemicals.
What?
But Milind and Zoya said…
Puneet, track their phones.
Sir, it's out of coverage.
Their last known location
is Orion Chemicals.
Thirty-seven minutes ago.
Puneet, send backup
to Orion Chemicals right away.
Alert all units.
We're on our way.
Fuck!
Stay with me, Milind.
Milind.
The disposal team is entering the core.
Disabled outlets for E1, E2, and E3. Over.
The scrubber tank is active.
Restarting the flare tower.
Nitrogen back to normal
levels in E1. Over.
"A major disaster averted,"
claim government sources.
"Casualties could've been in
thousands," says the Home Minister.
This is the first-ever incident
after the 1984 Bhopal Gas Tragedy.
The Delhi Police categorically maintain…
The Central Government
has set up a high alert…
The government is blowing its own trumpet.
Gentlemen, listen up!
We cannot appear to be weak.
We cannot let this be a terrorist win.
Send him in.
Mr. Ahuja, the CEO of Orion Chemicals.
Before we go any further,
Mr. Ahuja, let me tell you,
whatever we say in this room today…
remains in these four walls.
You know, we cannot…
call this a terrorist attack.
It was…
a gas leak.
Equipment failure.
An accident.
But sir, this is--
Whatever reason you pick for the gas leak…
it better be technically sound.
There are several experts on Twitter…
who will dig deep and find out
any flaw in anything.
But sir, it's not right.
Mr. Ahuja, would you like us
to pin this on your employee?
The… the one who helped the terrorists?
-What's his name?
-Vaibhav Therani.
-Sorry?
-Vaibhav Therani, sir.
-He was under pressure!
-Sri!
We have already announced that we
have stopped a major terrorist attack.
We can't tell them we failed now.
Mr. Ahuja, this is your only choice.
But sir, this will cause
serious damage to our brand image.
Mr. Ahuja, this is not a request!
Look, Mr. Ahuja.
I'll ensure that your company gets a grant
from one of the government's schemes.
It'll cover all your losses.
Thank you for your cooperation, Mr. Ahuja.
You may leave.
Sharma!
Thank you.
Anything else, Sri?
What is it? You can tell me.
I am done.
Done?
Sri, please!
Hello, gentlemen!
Please! Have a seat!
I only have six minutes,
so let's not waste time.
Sambit, start, please.
-Have a look.
-And please, have a seat.
We've received intel that…
the younger brother of Bhaskaran, Subbu…
Subramaniam Palanivel
is in Chennai right now.
He's there lobbying with his benefactors,
and then, these pro-rebel voices will
rally together to gain recognition…
for their Government in Exile.
The Lankans want Subbu, so I was
discussing possible options with madam.
Madam, he is the Foreign Minister of
the Lankan Tamil Government in Exile!
And you want us to hand
him over to the Lankans?
There will be a huge uproar!
It's a bad idea.
It'll lead to utter chaos!
You just handle your
external affairs' work.
Leave the handling of the chaos…
to me.
But ma'am,
he is not a wanted man in India.
So?
He's wanted by our allies.
May I just ask, why are we doing this?
I just don't get it!
Mr. Kulkarni…
the whole world was laughing when China
built a port in Southern Sri Lanka.
I won't allow the same
mistake to repeat itself.
If they manage to get
a stronghold in Sri Lanka…
then the Indian Ocean is gone forever.
I want this port deal at any cost.
Madam, allow me to say
that this is a very bad idea.
Yes, I agree with Kulkarni.
The repercussions of this in Tamil Nadu--
I see the big picture.
I don't mind making a few people unhappy
for us to beat the Chinese.
I am fine with that.
I will put up with it.
So, now, tell me. If we did have
to hand Subbu over to the Lankans…
then what would be your plan of action?
The building doesn't
even have an elevator.
My legs are fucked.
Sir!
Won't you invite us in?
Please.
Give me a glass of water!
Why doesn't your elevator work?
How does he live in this mess?
Comfy now?
How are you, Milind?
How's your therapy coming along?
It's going fine.
Milind, come back to work.
If you're at work, you
will be able to divert your mind.
But all this shit happened
because of my work.
Don't listen to these guys.
They're idiots,
chattering among themselves.
Whenever you feel alright, you can
join back. Okay? Take your time.
What do you mean?
Okay.
All right! Take your time,
but then, how much time?
Staying here all alone isn't going to
help. It will just end up driving you mad.
It's better for him if he
keeps himself busy, Tiwari.
The two guards…
I should have confronted
them as soon as we got there.
They didn't even look like guards.
My instinct kept telling
me that something's fishy.
Zoya and I even went back there…
but we had no evidence, and what
can you do without any evidence!
We decided to give them
the benefit of the doubt.
Motherfucking "benefit of the doubt!"
I should've just killed
them when I had the chance.
Milind! Milind!
It wasn't your fault.
Go tell Zoya that!
It wasn't her fault either!
It's all on me, it's all my failure, sir.
I've let you down, sir.
Did I ever tell you about Sujoy?
Remember?
Do you remember?
I did tell you.
Sujoy?
I was in Nagaland, in Kohima.
We had received intel
about an arms smuggler.
We wanted to nab him.
We were waiting outside the cafe.
But our asset, our informer…
didn't give us the signal.
We waited for an hour.
There was this one guy inside the cafe.
My instinct kept saying that
he's the guy we're after.
Before I could follow my instinct,
the smuggler figured out he's surrounded.
And he fired at us.
And Sujoy was shot dead… on the spot.
Fuck! When did this happen, boss?
Fuck!
After that incident… I felt so guilty.
I was miserable.
My kids were still very young, and
Suchi didn't know how to help me.
But one fine morning, Milind…
I woke up.
And I realized…
boss, this is the job.
And this is the risk.
We cannot sit and blame ourselves.
Milind, you put your life at risk
that day, which saved countless lives.
All of Delhi would have been annihilated.
Completely wiped out.
They would have been
choking on toxic gases.
Sir, then, why did you quit TASC?
Tiwari, you haven't changed.
You still have the touch.
What do you mean?
I mean, Sujoy.
What about Sujoy?
That Sujoy story wasn't made up?
Fuck! Sorry, man. I didn't know.
You never told me about him.
You're fucking kidding me.
That actually happened? Damn!
Sir, the MLA, Mathivazhagan,
is here to see you.
Okay, sir.
Wait for me.
Subbu, my brother. How are you?
And how's Bhaskaran doing?
He's fine. How's your health?
Where do I even start!
They say that I have
BP, sugar, and whatnot.
And now, they say I have a small kidney
stone for which I'll need surgery.
But forget all that!
It's so good to see you
after such a long time.
It warms my heart.
Now, I finally feel like I am at peace.
Likewise,
it's great to see you after so long.
-Mathi.
-Yes?
Looks like I need your help again.
Please, don't use big words like "help!"
Just tell me what you need,
and it'll be done!
Get some MLAs and MPs to talk favorably
about us to the Indian Government.
If India recognizes our
Government in Exile,
it will be a massive
victory for our cause.
Brother, I am not sure
how Delhi will react to this.
That woman… Basu?
She is so arrogant.
She doesn't like people like us!
The show she put on with
Rupatunga at the SAARC summit!
Unbelievable!
Brother, sorry!
I didn't intend to remind you
of Rupatunga and hurt you.
Forget all that.
I'll do what I can to rally support…
and bring this up for discussion
in the assembly, okay?
Long live Tamil!
Let's go.
Muthu Pandian.
Subbu is staying at that lodge.
You guys won't kill him, right?
You don't need to worry about all that.
We got this.
Thanks.
Sir, Subbu's identity has been confirmed.
-Do you have the team in place?
-Yes, sir!
How long will you take to
move in and pick up Subbu?
-One hour, sir.
-Go ahead!
I'll talk to the Mumbai TASC team,
and send you an officer-in-charge.
-Hand over Subbu to him.
-Yes, sir!
Make sure you keep this off the books.
No local cops to be involved.
Keep it low-key.
Yes, sir!
Subbu, how are you?
Everything all right?
Yes, I am doing fine here. Don't worry.
I have some good news.
Three people have agreed to talk
about our cause in the assembly.
An MP has even promised
to bring it up in the parliament.
It's a great start.
However, it isn't going to be that easy.
Anyway, when are you coming back?
I am meeting a couple more people
for funds and will leave tomorrow.
Be very careful.
Don't let that anger of yours
get the better of you, got it?
Up!
Who are you?
-Search the room.
-Yes, sir.
Check the suitcase.
What the hell is going on?
I am a Switzerland citizen!
You don't have the right to do this!
I am going to call the embassy!
Sir, we are just following orders.
I suggest you cooperate with us.
Let me make a call first!
I am not some average
Joe that you can fuck over.
We all know just who you are.
Okay.
You know what?
If you want to shoot me, go ahead…
-but I am getting out of here.
-Stay right there!
Brother, don't touch me again. Ever.
People have died just
for talking back to me.
Please, calm down.
Watch him.
Yes, sir.
You stay here.
Is everything okay, sir?
Oh! All good.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Some tea or coffee?
No, no. I am good. Thank you.
Let me know if you need anything.
Our agent from Mumbai
will be here any minute now.
Secure Subbu and bring him
to the back entrance.
Copy.
Get up.
Vasanth! Raghu! Come in! Vasanth?
Move! Go that side!
Cover all the exits!
Go that way!
You, this way!
Go.
I want him alive!
Subbu!
I want people on the second floor!
Secure the roof!
Ashok, check what happened!
What happened?
A man has fun and the world can't bear it.
-Take him to the hospital!
-Okay, sir.
Who's there?
Sir! Sir! It's not what you think, sir!
Sir, sir! We are a couple!
We are lovers, sir!
Sir! Sir!
Sir! It's my birthday today, sir!
Hey!
Shut up!
One more word and I will kill both of you.
Subbu!
Please don't harm the innocent civilians!
Asshole! I don't care!
One more word from you,
and people are going to die!
Subbu, there is no way you can escape!
Listen to what I am saying!
Phone.
-Can I make an international call?
-No, sir.
-Tiwari, I am busy!
-Just talk to me for a minute, fucker!
Talpade?
-Hi.
-Muthu Pandian.
JK.
What the hell is going on here?
We sent our team to bring
him to the back entrance.
He managed to overpower
us and killed our men.
You mean, an unarmed man
overpowered our trained agents?
Mr. JK, if you read the reports properly…
you'll know that Subramaniam
Palanivel isn't your average Joe.
-Listen, Mr. Muthuswamy--
-Muthu Pandian!
Yes, Muthu Pandian. Please understand,
our orders come directly from Delhi.
And we need to bring the situation
under control before it is too late.
I understand.
We've secured all the exits. Every
floor is manned by our personnel.
Just ensure that no civilian
enters the premises.
And the ones who are already inside,
keep them locked and secure.
Got that, boys?
And until I say so, nobody here
will use their weapon, alright?
Fucker thinks he's a big stud.
If you have any questions, ask!
What did you just say?
Merely translated what you just said.
But I said quite a bit?
Tamil is a precise language. Come.
What emergency do you have?
Listen, let's meet for lunch? My treat.
I am in Chennai.
In the middle of a hostage situation.
-What?
-I'll talk to you later.
Wait, wait, wait!
Tell me what's happening there.
We were supposed to take
a suspect to the safe house,
but that guy killed some of our men…
and is now cooped up
in a room with two hostages.
-Who's working with you?
-Local TASC officers.
And who's the subject?
I can't divulge the details to you!
You little fuck, just tell me!
Subramaniam Palanivel.
Do you remember the Sri Lankan rebels?
What the fu…
My sister is visiting us for Rakhi.
What nonsense are you talking about?
I don't have time for this shit!
Wait, listen!
Can't they call in the NSG for this?
No, we can't.
Kulkarni is very clear.
This operation is totally off the books.
There can be no leaks.
We have direct orders from Delhi.
I think, either the NSA
or PMO is involved.
Brad!
No, no! I'll be sending those TPS reports…
-What?
-to Andrews.
I'll also be changing the font color.
Yeah… back to blue.
And I'll be adding some colorful stuff!
What the fuck are you blabbering about?
Are you high?
My manager just stopped by.
Screw that, what were you saying?
The fucker, Subbu, refuses to negotiate.
I'll call you later, okay?
Don't call back! Enjoy the AC!
Bye, Talpade! Bye!
Weren't you just talking to Brad?
Yes, I was… and then, I switched the call.
So, personal call?
Sort of, semi-personal.
Remember, Srikant!
Don't be a "minimum guy."
Okay?
Good!
Yes?
Any update? Has Subbu made any demands?
Oh. I am so sorry, sir.
It completely slipped my mind
to give you hourly updates! Sorry!
Shove your sarcasm up your ass!
You're suffering from FOMO.
FOMO?
Fear of missing out, Uncle!
I am trying to help you.
I had an interesting idea
that I wanted to share with you.
But if you don't want it, that's fine!
FOMO, LOLO, ROFLO…
take it all up your ass.
JK! Just hear me out for a minute!
All right, tell me.
Chellam!
Who the hell is Chellam?
You don't know who Chellam is?
Can we play "Who wants to be
a millionaire" some other time?
I am in the middle of a hostage situation!
Chellam is the legendary agent…
who used to run missions in
Sri Lanka during the civil war.
And I think he is close
friends with Bhaskaran.
And our current RAW Chief
was mentored by Chellam.
Tell Sharma to call Chellam right away.
He's retired now, but that won't matter.
Are you serious?
No, I am making up stories
just to mess with you!
Just do as I say!
-Yes, JK. Tell me.
-Sir, we need help.
Srikant thinks that Chellam is
the key to negotiate with Subbu.
Srikant?
Sir, Srikant has offered to help.
Mr. Chellam! How are you?
Wrong number.
Yes, Srikant. Tell me.
You are the most cautious
man on the planet.
You're back? I was wondering
when I'd get a call.
Just didn't expect it would be you.
Srikant!
Well… yes.
I don't quite know what to say, sir.
You must be aware that, you know, there's
a hostage situation in Chennai, sir.
Yes, I know.
That Subbu situation
has gotten out of hand.
Yes, sir. And we need your help.
I am a retired old man.
What help can I offer?
And why are you getting involved?
Didn't you retire?
Yes, I did. Same as you, sir.
But these are exceptional circumstances,
and we need your help.
Tell me, how can I help?
Sir, you'll have to speak
to Subbu's brother, Bhaskaran.
I know he will listen to you.
Mr. Chellam!
Listen to me carefully.
-Hello?
-Hand the phone to Subbu.
Tell him his brother,
Bhaskaran, wants to talk.
Bhaskaran wants to talk to his brother.
Subbu! Your brother, Bhaskaran,
wants to talk to you!
I am leaving my gun
here and coming to you.
Don't play games!
Trust me! Please, talk to your brother!
I am approaching you.
I am unarmed!
Don't shoot!
Hello? Brother?
Subbu… listen to me carefully.
These bastards tried to arrest me.
-I want to kill all of--
-Subbu!
Shut up and listen to me, okay?
Okay.
Surrender.
Brother!
Are you nuts?
I'd rather die!
Subbu… don't do anything stupid.
-I don't have a good feeling about this.
-Subbu.
Just do as I say.
Out, out, out!
Hope that was a good catch-up.
Now, give me the phone.
Oh, shit!
Motherfucker!
Talk to the traffic police,
and clear our routes.
Sharma is going to shit on me.
It was supposed to be simple and brief,
but it turned out to be a nightmare.
It has only begun.
Since he has killed officers, they
have taken him into judicial custody.
TASC will have to apply for his custody.
Fucking asshole!
Why did he have to break my phone!
Our sources in Chennai tell us
that Sri Lankan rebel leader…
Subramaniam Palanivel is now under arrest.
Subbu is the younger brother of
Bhaskaran, who is a former rebel leader,
and is currently the Head of
the Sri Lankan Government in Exile.
A Home Ministry representative
has revealed that…
PM Basu is monitoring
the situation closely.
However, no official statement has
been released about Subbu's arrest.
Why do you look so happy?
That's because today,
I have outdone myself.
Whom did you shoot?
Are you crazy?
When will you give me a gun?
Why the hell do you want a gun?
Why not? I'll also need
a silencer, so that--
Get me one with a silencer,
so that no one finds out.
Do you know what the world's
most powerful weapon is?
What is it?
Brains. Right here.
Where is Dhriti?
Use your world's most powerful
weapon and find out where Dhriti is.
Listen, stop here.
I'll walk home from here.
Sure.
-Bye, Kalyan.
-Bye, Dhriti.
ALL OKAY?
YES, JUST DROPPED HER OFF AT HOME.