They are attacking us!
Brother Selva!
C4!
Bastards!
Bury this near Point Pedro.
It will come in handy.
And note down the GPS coordinates.
-Got it?
-Yes, sir.
One, two, three.
-Happy birthday!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, dear Suchi!
-Thank you!
-Happy birthday!
Hurry up, buddy.
Or you'll just have
the candles left to eat.
No worries! You finish the rest
of the song next year, okay?
Next year! Sounds good!
That's enough! Stop now!
-Happy birthday!
-Thank you!
-Blow it.
-Okay, okay.
-You want me to take it?
-Yes!
-Hold it up there.
-Up?
Yes.
Is it okay now?
-Can you see me?
-Yes!
Goddammit, I can't see a thing!
So, you are still in touch with him?
No, I mean…
sometimes, he calls me or texts me.
And what do you say?
Nothing.
There isn't much to say.
But you do reply, don't you?
Do you look forward
to his messages and calls?
Suchitra, I am not going to judge you.
I am your counselor.
Talk to me.
I don't like this state that I am in.
Sri is doing all he can to keep
me and the kids happy.
And I am just projecting
this mental state on him…
despite knowing the fact
that he's not at fault.
Am I the bad guy? I mean--
Let me be the counselor.
So, what do I do?
Life is 10% what happens to you,
and 90% how you react to it.
I mean, move on.
I know it's easy for me to say…
but forget about the past.
And move forward.
There is something that
I have figured out about you.
You have always been a working woman.
I am not saying homemakers
don't have tough jobs.
But sitting at home all day…
is not the best idea for you.
They say, "An idle mind knows not
what it wants, an idle mind…"
I feel like I am living a lie.
Should I talk to Sri about this?
I don't know if you'll be
able to live with your lie.
But will Srikant be able
to live with the truth?
There is unrest across Tamil Nadu.
Protests are happening everywhere.
Intel chatter is indicating
that there will be retaliation.
Focus on that angle, Kulkarni.
-But our focus has always been on--
-Our London office has informed us.
We have a serious problem on our hands.
Have a look.
Major Sameer and Bhaskaran.
With Major Sameer backing him, Bhaskaran
is going to become a huge problem for us.
According to the Intel from RAW,
they are plotting to assassinate the PM.
What?
Please ask the PM to cancel her meeting
with the Sri Lankan President in Chennai.
This isn't just any ordinary meeting.
PM Basu has a point to prove.
Send your best people to Chennai, okay?
Sambit, how about some tea?
Some other time.
Kulkarni has a special unit…
and they just have one job!
To predict the attacks!
And if they can't even do that,
what's the point of funding them?
Thanks to you, Lankans are happy.
Subbu is out of the equation.
A political prisoner has
been killed in our custody!
The world's intelligence
community is laughing at us!
Thank God…
I've managed to maintain
a healthy relationship
with the Sri Lankan President.
Ma'am, we think Sameer
and the Tamil rebels are collaborating.
And?
And…
Sameer wants to take
advantage of Subbu's death…
and fire over the rebels' shoulder.
Ma'am, I think…
they are planning to strike.
And I am the target?
That's what the intelligence
suggests, ma'am.
Ma'am, I highly recommend that
until this threat is neutralized…
you should cancel your public appearances.
Mr. Sambit!
The talks to be held in Chennai with
the Lankan President have been announced.
Neither the date and time…
nor the venue will be changed.
You do your job.
It is your responsibility
to keep us both alive.
Ma'am, at least, change
the venue to another city.
The day Basu starts to fear these
black flags and baseless threats…
will be the day she resigns.
But ma'am…
-the risk is very high.
-Good day!
Good day, ma'am.
Give me a minute.
One cigarette, please.
Hey, Salman! Don't forget your change.
You smoke?
Yeah, you want a drag?
What the hell!
Why did he call you Salman?
All studs are called Salman.
Greetings, brother.
Sajid.
By the grace of Allah, the first
phase of our mission was successful.
Phase two will start soon.
I'll contact you. Stay in Chennai for now.
Brother… there's something
I need to take care of.
I'll be back in a week.
What could be so important, Sajid?
Some unfinished business in Mumbai that--
Right now,
nothing matters more than the mission.
God willing…
we will soon achieve our goal.
Forget everything else for now.
Focus on the mission.
It's an order.
Goodbye.
I don't know.
-Yes, brother.
-Where are you?
I am with the girl.
Stop seeing her.
From today, you'll neither
see her nor talk to her.
Completely cut off.
So, the plan is canceled?
Yes.
Goodbye.
What happened?
Nothing. Shall we leave?
Okay.
Chennai?
The whole team?
So, going there to investigate
Subbu's assassination?
For that, and there's
some other stuff as well.
Are you sure you don't want
to come to Chennai with us?
If I go there,
who will take care of my family?
So thanks, but no thanks, darling.
Hang on, I'll show you
a couple of darlings.
Sameer and Bhaskaran are working together.
Kulkarni will ensure you're
the Employee of the Month.
And I'll handle Suchi.
You know, it's Suchi's birthday today.
I am taking her to her
favorite restaurant for dinner.
Srikant!
Personal work?
Yes! This is JK Talpade.
-He's a very good friend of mine,
-Hi!
and that's Tanmay Ghosh, my manager.
He just dropped in to say hi to me.
Just give me two minutes.
Okay, then. I'll just go to my room
and wait on your TPS reports now.
Great, yeah. Thank you.
So…
Busy?
This fucker!
See you.
Sir…
Rajalekshmi! Please have a seat!
My eldest kid is 12 years old.
The younger one is nine years old.
They are my life.
Do you have any siblings?
Not anymore.
What?
My younger brother died in an accident.
Oh, I am sorry.
Anyway, would you like some coffee or tea?
No, sir. Thank you.
"Thank you."
Is that Sri Lankan Tamil?
Get me a coffee.
Sir, I want to resign.
Why?
Is there a problem?
Is it the money? I'll give you a raise.
Do you want to take a break
for a couple of months?
No, sir. Nothing like that.
Is someone bothering you at work?
My mother is unwell.
I have to go back to my hometown.
I hope it's not something serious.
They say that her days are numbered.
Give it to her.
Have it, Raji.
Don't worry.
I'll relieve you in a couple of days.
And if you need any financial
assistance, don't hesitate to ask me.
I am here to help.
Thank you, sir, but I'll manage.
-Thank you very much, sir.
-Please, drink your coffee!
What's the rush?
Mixed veg in Schezwan sauce.
That'd do. Serve it here.
Jasmine rice.
Just one, just one! Yeah, thank you.
Yeah, that's fine. Thanks.
-Yeah.
-Mushroom in XO sauce.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy your dinner.
-Okay.
How is it?
Oh, sorry. Please.
Good?
Do you like it?
Sri.
There's something I want
to discuss with you.
It's been on my mind for a long time.
What?
I am thinking of going
back to work at ShrinkMe.
Oh, Arvind's company?
It's not his company.
Of course! I meant…
where Arvind works.
I never really understood.
Why did you quit?
And now, why do you want to go back?
Am I not allowed to change my mind?
Why are you getting defensive?
Don't be so innocent, Srikant!
I know what you're trying to do.
What am I trying to do?
You're bringing up Arvind
just to piss me off.
I know you have a problem with him.
Problem? I have no problem with him.
I thought you have a problem,
that's why you left the job.
What's with all these questions?
All these questions?
I just asked you one thing.
Why are you making a big deal out of this?
Suchi, why can't we talk
about anything peacefully?
Can you even remember the last time we
had a chat without breaking into a fight?
If I am really that bad, then why
are we even together, Srikant?
I am the one who fights!
I am the one at fault!
No romance! No se--
Sure! That's great! Scream louder!
Tell everyone here about our sex life!
Enough is enough!
I've been trying very hard for a year now.
I really have.
I left TASC and found myself a 9 to 5 job.
I drop the kids off at school.
I bring them back home.
I help you at home. I take time out.
I've been trying everything possible
to make you happy, Suchi!
But nothing ever seems to make you happy!
Wow, Srikant Tiwari! Wow!
So, you think you are doing me a favor?
This is what a father does!
This is what a husband does!
You thought you'd get a medal
at the end of all this?
I've been doing this our whole marriage.
For months, you wouldn't be home,
and I was doing everything on my own!
I was alone at the
Parent-Teacher meetings!
I was alone at the doctor's appointments!
Years of being alone,
and no companionship!
And all of a sudden, you want
to be crowned Husband of the Year?
You quit your job at TASC, right?
Please! Join them back!
I have been doing all this by myself
for all these years!
And I can still do it!
During Atharv's delivery,
I took myself to the hospital.
It has been nine years, Suchi!
And you're going on and on about
it like a goddamned stuck record!
I was in Delhi--No, no.
I was in Kolkata at that time!
Really?
You told me you were in Dehradun.
How much more will you lie, Srikant?
I only lied to protect you from my truth.
You know the kind of work I used to do.
I lied so that you could sleep peacefully.
I could protect you.
I could protect my family!
Right.
You should join politics, Srikant.
You aren't even trying
to hide your lies anymore.
You justify your lies these days.
You know what?
Our whole marriage is a sham!
Sham?
Sham, yeah?
"The thing that is not
what it is purported to be."
Now, what the fuck does "purported" mean?
"Falsely present something as the truth."
"Bogus."
So, you think our marriage is bogus?
You know what?
I think we need to take some
time off from each other.
Time off?
Yeah.
What's going on, Suchi?
What's going on?
I haven't been in a great
mental state lately.
No, that I can see.
Crystal clear!
Srikant, do you even understand
what I am trying to say?
No, I don't want to understand.
I don't understand western culture.
"Let us take time off from each other.
Let us take a break from each other."
I don't get it!
Where I come from, either you are
married, or you are not.
There is nothing in between.
I can't believe this!
What is it that you want?
Just tell me that!
What the fuck do you want?
Tell me what it is!
-I am done!
-I am also fucking done!
Sir, is madam coming back?
Suchi! What is this?
What?
You were supposed to send me
that report like five hours ago!
What?
I am having a really bad day.
Just leave me alone.
Excuse me?
Oh, man! Please!
Please, leave me alone.
My conference room! Now!
Follow me!
Listen!
I won't mince my words!
The only reason you got this
job is because of your brother!
And I tried to respect your age.
But there is a certain order in
this office and I cannot tolerate--
Motherfucker! I've heard enough!
You get on my nerves!
Nobody--
Don't say another word!
If I hear a squeak out of you, I'll…
No, but--
You can't--
-How dare you--
-What did I just tell you?
If you hear a squeak out of me, you'll--
What did I just say?
Moron!
I quit!
Stupid fuck!
Security!
Hello!
Sir, I have…
quit my job.
Welcome back to TASC, Srikant!
Thank you, sir.
Raji!
Just a minute.
I need to discuss something
important with you.
I'll be waiting in my car, at the back.
When do you leave for your hometown?
The day after tomorrow, sir.
So, you're here for another day.
Where did you say you come from?
Jaffna?
Many immigrants give fake addresses…
before joining us.
While verifying your address,
I discovered that you
had given a fake address.
So many people work under me.
It was not that hard to figure out.
A few months ago,
the cops showed up at the factory.
They wanted to check
the employee register.
People no longer have
sympathy for refugees.
Don't worry.
I didn't give you up to the cops.
Are you going back to Jaffna?
Sir, what are you getting at?
I like you, Raji.
That's why I am trying to help you.
I don't expect much in return.
My wife isn't in town.
I don't know what I am
going to have for dinner.
Why don't you invite me over for dinner?
What do you say?
By the way…
Nikhil keeps asking about you.
How is he?
Must be really pissed
off because I quit so abruptly.
Not really.
Also, the ShrinkMe app is soon going to
touch the milestone of one million users.
That's great!
Congratulations!
To you, too.
You played a big part in
getting ShrinkMe this far.
What did you want to talk about?
Yeah…
I still have a stake at ShrinkMe, right?
Of course! Of course!
I know, it isn't much.
It's just seven percent, but…
it's very significant to me.
I…
Do you want to vest your stake?
No, no, no!
I…
I want to come back.
I want to come back and work at ShrinkMe.
That's great!
Of course,
you can come and join us anytime.
In fact, Nikhil will be very
thrilled when he gets to know.
Thank you.
It's…
it's really great to have you back.
By the way…
how are the kids?
And Srikant?
I heard, he's found
himself a corporate job.
Yeah.
-Excuse me, bill please.
-Sure, ma'am.
Suchi.
I keep on thinking about…
I think…
we should talk sometime.
You've never had a drink?
Chennai has gone to the dogs!
Women are now smoking
and drinking like they're men.
Our culture has gone to shit.
I know what you're thinking.
How a gentleman like me…
can drink…
and eat nonvegetarian food, right?
I drink because…
it increases my stamina.
If you know what I mean.
I am not forcing you, Raji.
I have your consent… right?
I have your acceptance towards it… right?
Earlier, when I mentioned
the cops, your face fell.
Did you do some stupid shit
in Jaffna and run away?
Tell me, Raji.
Did you get scared?
Don't be scared.
Your secret is safe with me.
Why are you standing there?
Come here.
Sit.
Take off your top.
Damn, you are so fit!
Bitch!
Don't act like you don't like this!
I know many whores like you.
All I asked for was some good company!
Just finish quickly.
Bitch!
Are you mocking me?
Bitches like you deserve to be shot!
What the hell do you think of yourself?