Help!
Please, help!
Help! Somebody help!
Help!
Mom!
You bastard!
Why are you doing this? Please, tell me.
Here's some food. Eat.
-Leave me!
-Hey!
Eat!
Hey!
Enough is enough!
I trusted you, Kalyan.
Please, let me go. Please, I beg of you!
Please, Kalyan. Please, I want
to go back to my mom-dad. Please!
-It is not in my hands.
-Please!
I just do what they ask me to do.
What?
Who are they?
Have you lost it?
There's no point in screaming.
Nobody can hear you.
My father doesn't have
much money to pay you.
You are here because of
your father, understood?
What?
All Srikant Tiwari has ever
done is kill innocent people
in the name of the country!
That's all!
What the hell are you talking about?
My father is a normal guy!
Normal guys don't work for the NIA.
-N-I what?
-Your father is a secret agent!
He works for infidels
and takes innocent lives!
And to all my brothers, he's been a--
There has been a misunderstanding.
My father works for an IT company.
He's a normal guy!
This is all a big mistake!
Kalyan, please!
Is your name even Kalyan?
Who are you?
Kidnapper?
Gangster?
Go on.
Terrorist?
That's how all of you see us, right?
Eat.
You are going to be here for a while.
Yes, Atharv just ate.
He's about to leave for school.
I don't know…
how can a mother not know
where her daughter is?
Dad, please listen to what I am saying.
How am I supposed to know?
She said she was going
to the mall with Mahima!
Mahima says she has no idea!
What I am trying to say is…
I am sorry, Dad. I am sorry.
I will call you once she's back home.
Her name is Raji. She is a trained pilot.
Selvarasan studied aviation
engineering in Ireland.
So, you think they are
planning an air attack?
Pretty sure. Especially, since
Raji and Selva are involved.
A plane packed with all the C4 they stole
from Point Pedro is like a guided missile.
We have to send a high alert signal
to all the airports immediately.
Besides Meenambakam Airport, I want
a list of all the private airstrips…
and flying schools in the nearby vicinity.
I want it right now! Immediately!
On it, sir.
How is Suchi doing?
She is… she's trying to be strong.
I can't believe Dhriti has a boyfriend.
We don't even realize when kids grow up.
Tiwari, I should have been
there with you right now.
If only--
Deep down, I knew my job would
have repercussions on my family.
I am sure that has happened.
What's the update there?
New intel suggests that the rebels
are planning a kamikaze-style attack.
Shit!
Have you put the DGCA
and Air Force in the loop?
Tiwari, stop worrying about what's
happening here. I will handle it.
You just focus on Dhriti.
I am sure she will be home soon.
Okay then, bye.
Srikant.
What happened?
I am so sorry about all this.
Seriously, if you need anything
at all, please let me know.
That's alright. Thank you.
Thanks.
Bye.
Bye, Suchi.
When was the last time you met Dhriti?
We went to the inter-school
culturals, two weeks back.
How was Dhriti then?
I mean, well, she was just being Dhriti.
She fought with the
judges and called them…
sexist assholes.
She was like a sister to me, Uncle.
So, we never really spoke to each other.
She doesn't like people from the town.
She called me a capitalist baboon.
-What?
-Capitalist baboon?
Dhriti and I, we developed
some ideological differences.
So, we weren't really that tight.
She's a feminazi and I am a libertarian.
I am more old-style.
What is this feminazi?
It was Kalyan's birthday yesterday,
so they went to a movie…
at Infinity.
After that, they went over to his house.
Is Kalyan here at school?
He's not from our school, Uncle.
-Which school is he from?
-I don't know.
-What do you mean?
-I mean, he looks older, so…
Do you happen to have his photograph?
No.
Actually, when I tried taking
a selfie with him, he didn't let me.
-Why?
-He is kind of shy, I think.
I don't know!
Okay, what is his phone like?
Phone?
It's one of those old-style,
non-touch, keypad phones.
Okay, Mahima!
You know right,
that Kalyan and Dhriti were…
What, Uncle?
Excuse me, ma'am.
Can you just give us two minutes?
Thank you, ma'am.
Is it right that Dhriti and Kalyan
are girlfriend and boyfriend?
Is that a bad thing, Uncle?
No!
Everyone has a boyfriend,
all the girls in our class.
I mean, except me, of course.
Look, Mahima. If there is anything
else that you know about Dhriti…
then please, tell me.
If there is any secret between you
two, please tell me.
It is a very serious situation!
We can't find Dhriti!
Uncle, I have told you everything.
So, how did Dhriti and Kalyan meet?
Dhriti met him on Instagram, I think.
He has deleted his account.
This guy is a ghost.
Sri, I think, it's time for
you to tell Suchi about everything.
What?
That Dhriti has been kidnapped?
I have spoken to the airport authorities.
They've mailed me the list
of students and staff
from the Chennai Airport Flying Club.
And?
Dead-end.
But the AIA guy said there is
an independent flying school
on the Chennai-Bangalore highway.
-Tigris Aviation.
-Okay.
But it has been shut for a few months now.
Have you contacted Tigris Aviation?
The number is dead.
Should we go and check?
Sure, let's go!
Fucking hell!
Won't even let me eat in peace!
Sir, this way.
-Hello, sir.
-Hello.
Yes, show me.
Skip ahead.
Pause it! Pause it!
-Zoom in.
-Yes, sir.
Wait a second.
-Alright.
-Play on.
Show me where he exited from.
Yes.
Shit!
Why the long face?
Can you do it or not?
Yes, I can.
I have to shoot a video of you.
Need to see you cry.
If it hurts, then…
Please!
Please, don't hurt me.
I will just act it out.
Start recording.
Srikant Tiwari, do as you are told.
Fuck off!
Raji! Those bastards have come here, too!
Open the gate.
Sir, the company has shut down.
We are with the police. Open the gate.
Raji!
The car is coming in.
Are you going to open the gate
or someone else will do it?
Sir, what do you want?
Are you in charge here?
No, I am not.
I am just here to salvage the equipment.
I am not allowed to entertain
visitors without proper authorization.
We are the police department!
What other authorization do you need?
Fuck off!
Muthu, you check the plane.
I will see what's going on inside.
Sir, sir!
Sorry, but I can't let you check
the premises without permission.
What permission?
You are stopping a law enforcement
officer from doing his duty!
This investigation
concerns national security.
-In Tamil?
-Muthu, explain it to him, please.
So, you are impeding an investigation
that concerns national security.
-Out of the way!
-Sorry, sir. I can't let you.
Without permission we cannot
allow you inside, sir.
We should have come here with a warrant.
We did not come here planning to raid it.
What does it matter anymore? We need
a warrant if we have to do any inspection.
You both go…
and get a search warrant
from the magistrate.
-Okay, sir.
-What?
-I will talk to him over the phone.
Leave now.
Until the warrant comes,
they will be here only.
Tell this guy that I want to see all
the company permits, DGCA license with…
the certificate of incorporation.
Also, we need a list of all the people
who have been trained here.
-Show us the documents?
-License… document…
you can examine that, but I can't let you
search the premises without a warrant.
Where is everyone else?
He is salvaging all the
equipment by himself?
Where are the others?
Are you here to salvage
the equipment all by yourself?
I came here to survey the place.
He is here to survey.
Prabhu!
What is going on? Who are these people?
Sir, they are with the police.
Sir, there is nothing here.
In a few days, they will pull down this
hangar, too. The company has shut down.
Muthu, let us--
-What is your name?
-Karthik.
Where are you from?
-Trichy.
-He is our manager, sir.
No need for a warrant.
Just get permission from the owner.
Also, before you leave, please log
your visit in the visitor's book.
Sign in the visitor's book?
Do I look like a fucking tourist to you?
How long will you guys be here?
We will leave in a bit,
once we take the equipment.
Muthu! Muthu!
Don't fight.
Come here.
Let's think of some other way.
-Just one thing.
-What?
The manager…
when he first spoke…
it sounded like he was
talking in Sri Lankan Tamil.
Are you sure?
He was talking with a Jaffna accent.
"What's going on? Who are these people?"
Nobody speaks like that in Tamil Nadu.
Srikant, I have alerted all units, and
they are actively searching for Dhriti.
We will find her.
What is this?
Give it to me.
Srikant Tiwari, do as you are told.
I--
What do they want with our daughter?
-Suchi, calm down. Calm down.
-I just want Dhriti back!
-She will be back!
-I just want her back!
Suchi! Su--
We can't let them stay here for too long.
We have to get rid of them immediately.
Man! It's almost nighttime.
When will the warrant get here?
I'd told you it will take time.
Sir, I am leaving. You should too.
Come back tomorrow.
The warrant is on the way.
Once it is here, we will take half an
hour to search the place, so just wait.
-I can't. I have to go. Prabhu!
-Sir!
He will be here.
What did he say?
That one is going, this one will wait.
We have to wait, too. Fucking hell!
-Hello?
-Srikant Tiwari.
Oh, Sajid Ghani.
You have started kidnapping
children to achieve your goals?
Did you forget how you manipulated
Moosa's mother to achieve your goal?
You and I are the same.
We are both willing to do whatever
it takes to get what we want.
What do you want?
If you want your daughter back alive…
then you and your team need
to stay out of my way.
I want to talk to my daughter.
Srikant, if I were in your place…
I wouldn't play these games.
Hey!
I am not playing any games!
This is a matter of my daughter's life.
I just want to know if
she is alright, got it?
Eight o'clock.
He's using a scrambler.
Sorry.
Muthu!
You try to distract him.
-I will try to look around.
-What?
We can't wait any longer!
What did you say your name was?
Prabhu.
Where are you from?
Madurai, sir.
-From proper Madurai?
-Yes.
Oh, you came here from Madurai?
Yes, sir. Now, I am in Chennai.
Chennai?
Where in Chennai?
Kundrathur.
Oh, okay. What is this, Prabhu?
It would have taken us only ten minutes.
We would have finished our job and left.
Okay, forget it.
Okay, is there a tea shop nearby?
I have no idea, sir.
I think, it's a little far.
I just came here to survey, sir.
Fuck!
Shit! Shit!
Muthu!
JK!
Brother, shoot.
Careful!
They are running away!
The entire plane is
packed with explosives!
What?
Listen!
You go towards the fence and try
to escape. I will cover for you.
Let's go together.
Damn it! If we don't split up,
we will both die.
Go!
Hurry up, Muthu!
Hey, look over there.
Look, he is running!
Over there! He is getting away! Shoot him!
Hey! They are getting away!
Fuckers! I can't find them!
They have escaped!
Let's pack up and leave
before they return with backup.
Srikant, it's already 8:15 p.m.
They haven't called yet.
-They were supposed to call
-Suchi,
-15 minutes ago!
-Suchi, Suchi!
This is a usual tactic.
They just do it to make
the family anxious.
Don't worry, they will call.
Wait.
Hello?
Mom, I love you.
I am sorry about what I
said to you the other day.
I am really sorry, I didn't mean it.
It's okay, little one.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
I am okay.
-Dhriti!
-Dad!
Listen to me, okay? Pay attention.
I am listening, Dad.
Okay… Dhriti.
First of all, my child…
I love you, okay?
And…
I won't let anything happen to you.
I promise you, I will bring you back.
I hope Kalyan didn't hurt you.
No, Dad. He did not.
Is Kalyan with you?
-Yeah.
-Kalyan, my son.
If you can hear me, then tell
me, do you really love Dhriti?
What are you saying?
Or was your love for her
only an act, to kidnap her?
Dad, what are you saying?
Kalyan, I don't know
what your real name is,
but I know this much…
that if you love Dhriti…
then you won't let anything happen to her.
Dad, what are you even saying?
Dhriti!
Dhriti, listen to me carefully.
Man can truly feel alive only if
he finds a true connection in life.
Connection, my child.
The true meaning of life is only felt…
through ties of love.
Love is the only strength,
and only weakness, dear.
Do you understand what I am saying?
Love is a strength, but also a weakness.
Dad--
We have got nothing.
They are using Dhriti as leverage.
So that I do what they want me to do.
Well, go ahead.
Do it!
She is paying for your deeds.
I don't care what you do
and how you do it…
but I want my daughter back!
You get it?
Motherfucker!
-Yes, brother.
-Is Salman with you?
-Yes.
-Put me on speaker.
-Listen carefully.
-Yes, brother.
I will be there soon.
Syed, meet me on the highway.
Salman, get the camera ready.
Make sure the battery is fully charged.
I want to record her
screams before we kill her.
Get everything ready.
The video should make that
motherfucker want to kill himself.
Hang up.
Sri… RPF called. They have sent a video.
Show me.
This is from Dombivli station.
11:30 p.m., last night.
Here, look at this.
He dumped Dhriti's phone on the train…
and then, the phone traveled up
and down the line.
The fucker has used his brains well.
Check all the footage from the station's
surveillance cameras and traffic cameras.
And ask the Dombivli police station
to start their search immediately.
-Ajit, you come with me. Come on!
-Come, come! Come on, guys!
Have you seen this man?
No, sir.
Have you seen him somewhere?
-No, I haven't.
-Have you seen this man?
No.
Hello. Jeep 635?
Hello! Sub-Inspector Shinde here.
We are sending you pictures.
If you spot this man, be vigilant.
-And inform the headquarters immediately.
-Okay, okay. Copy, copy.
I will inform you immediately.
Over.
Head towards the station.
Looks like a couple of junkies.
Arrest them.
What's going on here?
Nothing, sir. Just smoking a cigarette.
-Cigarette?
-Yes, sir. Just smoking a cigarette.
Junkie asshole!
Put them in the car!
-Sir, we weren't doing anything.
-Shut up and get in the car!
What is this, sir?
I have never been arrested for this!
Yeah, let us go.
Looks like it is your lucky day.
I will give you a nice tip.
Please, leave us.
You want to go home, right?
Give me some information
and I will let you.
Have you seen this man?
Sir, I have seen him.
Where?
In Dombivli.
I know where he lives.
-Are you sure?
-Yes, sir.
Jeep 635, connect me to the headquarters!
So, it was all a lie?
-Yes, brother.
-Sajid and I are on the way.
Is everything set?
Yes, everything is ready.
Are you going to kill me?
I know you are going to kill me.
Please, please, let me go.
Please! Please, don't kill me!
-Let go of my hand.
-No, Kalyan. Please!
I am sorry, it's not in my hands.
Kalyan, please.
Dad was right that you love me.
I know you do.
Please!
Please! I swear,
I won't say anything to anybody!
Please, let me go!
Please! I swear on you, Kalyan!
Please!
I don't want to die.
I know somewhere you love me, too.
For a… for a second, please…
please untie me!
Please, Kalyan!
Let us leave from here.
You come with me.
Please!
Kalyan, please.
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
I knew you will let me go.
Please, drop me off at home.
I am sorry.
I can't let you go.
I am sorry, I can't!
Kalyan, no.
Please, I don't want to die.
He will kill me, Kalyan! Please!
Kalyan, please!