Raji?
Raji, can you hear me?
You'll be fine! Don't worry!
Medical kit!
The bullet went right through.
She's lost a lot of blood.
We need to disinfect the wound
and stop the bleeding.
Do you think we can handle it?
How are you?
Alive!
The doctor said you'll be discharged soon.
I just got off the phone
with Milind's parents.
We lost a good man, Sri.
I am really sorry!
How are you feeling?
I am alright, sir. I am perfectly fine.
Sajid was in Veeraranyam
with the rebel fighters.
I am sure he's working with Sameer.
We know that Sameer is providing
them logistical support.
But I am really surprised they
have a man on the ground.
Sir, Sajid isn't any ordinary asset.
We've already seen how dangerous he is.
I am aware of that.
Along with the bodies of Lankan soldiers
that were found at Point Pedro…
included the corpse
of an Indian civilian, as well.
And the description matches Jebaraj.
Jebaraj?
I am putting together
a special team to work closely
with the Tamil Nadu commando force…
for tactical ground support.
Sri, we have to stop
these people at all costs.
Sir, please convince the PM to delay
the bilateral talks with Sri Lanka.
Or change its location out of Chennai.
Sri, I am trying! Believe me!
You have no idea how stubborn PM Basu is.
She hates being cornered.
For now,
let's find out what their plan is.
Okay, sir.
The Lankans have found
Jebaraj's body at Point Pedro.
If Jebaraj and Raji…
went to Point Pedro together,
and if Raji knows that Jebaraj is dead…
then why did she go back to his house?
I am asking you again,
did Jebaraj tell you what he's up to?
He left last evening.
He hasn't come back since.
Where is he, sir?
Think calmly and tell me.
Okay, does Jebaraj keep anything hidden?
His life is in danger.
Tell us the truth if
you want him back alive.
Sir, he keeps everything in the storeroom.
I have never entered that room.
Storeroom?
JK!
Sri!
Raji came back to get the detonator.
They are planning an explosion.
I told that mad man!
The Indians will never support
us after this massacre.
Let us not assume that.
Should I talk to our people
there to try and fix this?
Shut up, Ravi.
The whole world is watching us.
Even the smallest of lapses
will have a big impact.
They will be all over us, again.
We need to find Bhaskaran
as soon as possible.
Hey, Mahima!
Hey! What's up, bro?
Listen, you have to cover for me today.
Kalyan?
Your mom's radar always catches our lies.
Her radar isn't working nowadays.
If she calls you, tell her
we're meeting at the mall.
Okay, listen!
-So, what's your plan?
-Sister!
A movie.
I've got to go, bye.
Open the door!
Sister!
What is it?
Can't you wait a little?
Where are you going all
dressed up like this?
Don't annoy me!
Where are you going?
I am meeting Mahima at the mall.
Boyfriend.
-When will you be back?
-In the evening.
Dinner?
I'll eat outside.
It's my friend's birthday.
Dhriti!
You've been going out every day.
-Can't you stay at home sometimes?
-What about you?
I barely see you at home!
I have a job to do!
And this is a home,
not a hotel or a lodge!
I am asking you something!
When will you be back?
It's my life, too!
I'll come when I am done!
Dhriti! I am--
You sent Papa away!
You happily go to your
office with your friend,
and you want me to stay at
this place all the time!
How selfish are you!
What!
Watch it!
You are still a child.
Behave like one.
I know what's going on.
Papa isn't coming home…
and you guys are getting a divorce.
It's okay, Mom.
Don't worry, I am there for you.
Deepan!
I heard you were trying to meet me.
Sameer!
Yeah.
Only you can help me.
I need to find Bhaskaran.
I don't know where Bhaskaran is.
You know what Bhaskaran is planning?
If a friend of 30 years has no idea…
then how would I know?
See, the future of our government
is at stake here, Sameer.
Could you please, at least, tell
Bhaskaran to get in touch with me?
As I told you, I don't know
anything about Bhaskaran.
If you need any other help, let me know.
Anytime. Anywhere.
I am always with you.
The police have circulated
our pictures all over.
We cannot leave this hangar
until the mission is complete.
By now, they would have
figured we are planning a blast.
Before they figure out the other details…
we need to get it done.
Here is a list of things
I need immediately.
It will take me ten to twelve
hours to build a new detonator.
Hurry up!
The signing starts at 11:00 a.m.
at the convention center…
which is located over here,
in the west wing of the hotel.
This is our target.
I've mapped the route for the plane.
This is the best route.
There aren't any high-rise
buildings in the vicinity.
The plane will stay under the radar.
If Raji maintains course
for the next 60 seconds…
she'll be able to hit the target.
The nose and sides of the plane
will have the greatest impact.
We should completely pack those parts
of the plane with C4.
For a more lethal, bigger explosion.
Karthik!
I need the items on this list, quickly.
Brother Selva.
Raji's fever is getting out of control.
What happened?
Raji…
Prabhu, you need to get a doctor.
Right.
Brother Selva.
If Raji is unable to fly, I'll do it.
Karthik. The plane has to fly
below 1,000 meters…
via Sunguvarchathiram,
towards the Chennai coast.
It isn't an easy task.
Not getting spotted by
the radar is not easy.
Only Raji can do it.
Mr. Deepan, it's been a while.
-What is it I can do for you?
-I want you to find this man.
Bhaskaran Palanivel.
Okay, I'll see what I can do.
Find him, Adrian.
Please, reconsider it, ma'am.
There is going to be an attack
on you is a certainty.
Please, postpone the meeting. Please.
Is this a joke?
Ma'am, Major Sameer is
supporting the rebels.
This intel is absolutely accurate, ma'am.
And what are you doing
about this information?
You increase the budgets every year.
If you can't make optimum
use of this money, tell me.
I can use it to fund
the Farmers' Welfare Program.
That is not fair, ma'am.
Despite you having all the resources…
a few rebels can shake up the country!
Is it fair?
I want to bring India
to the center stage of world politics…
and you people just--
There is a law of the jungle
that if the lion becomes weak…
the jackals get ready to feast.
Prime Minister Basu is
neither weak nor scared.
Ma'am, please go ahead
with meeting the President, but…
do it somewhere else.
It is a security nightmare, ma'am.
-The people here--
-They organized protests against me!
But I have a mother's heart.
When they were hit by floods,
I was the first one to get there.
I allotted a 500-crore relief package!
Whether it is life or politics,
when children start believing
that mother's love is unconditional,
they tend to get out of hand.
The meeting will happen in Chennai.
Where the hell have you brought me?
You're getting me into trouble,
aren't you?
-I am doubling my fee.
-Don't say you can't.
Money is not an issue.
Start the treatment.
Let's go!
Bullet wound?
I won't tell anyone.
Please let me go.
I can refer other doctors to you.
Doctor, trust me.
There is nothing to be afraid of.
You have the responsibility
to save a life.
Please, hurry up with the treatment.
I feel lost.
I am confused.
I've worked so hard on my family and…
now, it's all just falling apart.
I feel I am the reason, and…
I just hate myself!
I should talk to Sri.
I think I should.
-I just--
-Suchitra!
You know what people say?
"The truth will set you free.
Honesty is the best policy."
It's all bullshit.
If you tell Srikant the truth…
it will end your marriage.
I am telling you this
from personal experience.
Not as a counselor.
Don't do it!
-What happened?
-Nothing.
-Nice perfume, by the way.
-Don't change the topic.
Is everything alright?
Yes, everything is fine.
Did your dad find out about
me coming over to your place?
No. In fact, he's still out of town.
Like, 500 rupees for a ticket!
Let us just download
movies and watch them.
Yeah.
Listen, Dhriti…
What?
Nothing, I was just…
-Nothing!
-What is wrong with you, Kalyan?
Ever since we've met, you seem distracted.
We jinx it every time we kiss.
No, I didn't mean it like that.
I was just asking…
I don't know!
Actually, Mom and Dad aren't
going to be home for a while.
So, you are calling your girlfriend over?
I mean, girlfriend…
You are the worst
chicken I have ever seen.
Maybe, that is why, I feel safe with you?
Get your bike out.
I'll just inform Mom and be there.
Okay.
-Hi.
-Got any calls?
From your mom? No.
Good. I am doing homework with you.
-Are you serious?
-What do you mean?
You are staying over?
Listen, don't forget protection!
Please! I am not going
to do anything stupid.
But listen, whenever Mom calls you,
call me immediately, okay?
Yes.
And listen. Take care, okay?
Hello, Dhriti? Where are you?
I forgot my project report at Mahima's.
I am going to get it back.
-Dhriti, it's nearly eight o'clock!
-It's okay, Mom.
What it's okay? It's not okay!
Give me the address.
I'll come and pick you up.
Stop it, Mom. I'll take a rickshaw. Bye!
I know where she is.
-Tell me.
-Can I get chocolate?
Do I look like your father?
Where is she?
Mahima is just an excuse, Mom.
She has gone to see her boyfriend.
She doesn't have a boyfriend.
Mom, half a chocolate?
-Brushed your teeth?
-Yes. Didn't you see?
So, then it's settled, no chocolate.
Well played, Mom.
Muthu.
Tiwari.
To Milind.
To a hero.
We have to be vigilant now, got it?
Keep an eye on that side.
How are you feeling?
Just rest today.
You will feel better tomorrow.
My work here is done, Raji.
You're all set, too.
I am going to Mumbai in the morning.
I have some pending work there.
I've never met a soldier like you.
I will always remember this mission.
I am not saying this to please you.
I am lucky that I got to work with you.
Answer the phone, Dhriti.
The number you're trying to call is not--
-Hi, Auntie.
-Mahima, hi.
Is Dhriti with you?
Auntie, she just left.
She isn't answering her phone, so…
Auntie, her battery was low.
So, maybe, the phone is on silent.
Oh!
Alright.
Thanks, dear.
Okay! Good night, Auntie.
The number you're trying
to call is not answering.
Guys, the schedule for PM Basu
and Rupatunga's meet has been announced.
No change at all.
Damn! They screw around and we suffer.
I can die for the country,
but not for this petty politics.
You aren't putting your life at stake
for politics or some politician.
We are here to protect a position.
No matter who fills that position
and whatever their ideology is…
shouldn't matter to us. Governments
will come, governments will go.
National security is our duty.
Right?
Of course.
That is our bloody duty!
That is our bloody job!
We have to find Raji.
That is the only way
we can stop this attack.
Mahima, hi!
Sorry for calling you so late, but…
Dhriti has not come home yet.
Did she tell you where she was going?
Auntie, she left my place at nine o'clock.
Mahima, I spoke to you at ten o'clock,
and you said she had just left.
-Yes, Auntie. I meant to say--
-Mahima! Enough is enough!
Tell me where Dhriti is right now!
Or else, I am going to call the police!
Auntie, she--
Just tell me where she is!
No bullshitting! Tell me right now!
Actually, Auntie, Dhriti is out
on a date with her boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
Okay, what's his name?
Kalyan.
Do you have his number?
Sorry, Auntie…
but I don't have his number.
Do you know where they went?
After the movie,
she went over to his place.
Okay, give me his address.
I don't have it, Auntie.
Mahima, you are her best
friend and you know nothing?
Is he your classmate?
No, Auntie. They had met online.
Do you have a photo?
No, Auntie.
Actually, I've only met
him a couple of times.
Sorry, Auntie!
Enough now! How much will you drink?
Stop!
You drank all of this by yourself.
And then, you school me!
Pick up the phone!
Let it be.
What's with your ego, man?
She is still calling.
Just pick up the phone.
Hey!
Arvind?
Hey, hi.
Hi.
All okay?
Your marriage isn't a sham, you are!
Look, it's an unknown number.
That's more important than your wife,
right? I am sure you'll take this.
Hello?
Srikant, Arvind here.
Suchi's friend… colleague.
Oh, what happened?
Is Suchi okay?
Suchi has been trying to reach you.
Just talk to her.
Sri…
Dhriti hasn't come home yet.
Where is she?
With her boyfriend.
She has a boyfriend!
Who is he?
I don't know. Mahima said it
was some guy called Kalyan.
Where did she go with him?
I don't know, Sri.
How could you not know, Suchi?
What the hell is going on over there?
Stop yelling!
Okay, let me track her.
Put the phone down.
What happened?
Yes, Sri. Tell me.
I need your help to track a number.
For personal use?
It is bloody personal!
Sometimes, I wonder if I am working
for the government or you!
Why do you always make me do all this?
For God's sake!
I am sending you the number, okay?
You have to track it.
It's urgent.
Sure, send it to me.
Tiwari, will you tell me what happened?
Sri, we have tracked Dhriti's phone.
It was found on a local train.
We've questioned some commuters,
but no one has a clue.
-I am coming to Mumbai.
-Sri, maybe, she dropped her phone?
Ajit, I know my daughter.
She has never even lost a pin.
Something is wrong.
Are you suggesting…
We have to face the fact.
My daughter has been kidnapped.
And I hope…
I am wrong.
I'll be home by 5:00 a.m.
Did you find anything?
Her phone has been found on a local train…
but nobody has seen her.
She fought with me before leaving.
I had no idea she had a boyfriend!
We're trying to get
more details about Kalyan.
We've sent a team to Mahima's place, too.
She doesn't know anything!
She doesn't have his number or address!
She doesn't even have a photo with him!
Suchi, I will find Dhriti. It is my duty.