Raji, it's time for you
to meet someone. Come.
Chief!
I'd told you about Raji.
She's the best fighter pilot we have.
And she finished her
training in just six months.
Raji… I've heard a lot about you.
A sparrow became a hawk!
That too, within six months.
Is there anything else you'd like to say?
Do you have any new
justifications to offer?
Is there any new evidence you
want to manufacture against Kareem?
Or are you here to file a new sedition
case against Kareem's family or me?
Did they file a case?
I know my apology won't bring Kareem back…
but still.
I am…
I am sorry.
Easy for you to say that, sir.
You have blood on your hands,
but you still want a clean conscience.
I came here only to tell you the truth.
Kareem was not a terrorist.
He didn't deserve to die.
His death…
is on my conscience.
Take care.
I know you've recorded this conversation.
Use it however you want to.
I am willing to bear the consequences.
And as for the sedition
charges filed against you--
You don't need to do anything for me!
This is my country, too.
And I will fight the case with the system.
Okay.
And sir…
I will never forgive you.
Shankar, where's Nanda?
He hasn't come in today.
How well do you know Meyyappan?
He's my close friend and supporter.
He doesn't know about our plan.
It's just a sales deal for him.
Great.
Welcome, welcome!
I've been waiting for you!
I heard about Subbu, Chief.
Sorry for your loss.
Meet my friend, Mr. Arjun Singh.
-Hello.
-Good to meet you.
Let us sit.
Both my sons live in London.
They don't wish to run
the flying school in Chennai.
That is why I am selling it off.
Thanks for accepting my
offer, Mr. Meyyappan.
It's okay.
How old is your brother, Mr. Arjun Singh?
Vikrant is 26, Mr. Meyyappan.
It was heartbreaking when he was
refused admission on a physical condition.
That's why
I am buying him this flying school.
-So that he doesn't give up on his dreams.
-That is why…
God gave him a brother like you!
If you want,
we can sign the papers right away.
Now, you will only hear my words!
You will do everything as I say.
You will take me with you…
on a three-week holiday!
Shut up!
There will be no holiday!
Go to school and study!
Dad, you can't get
up in the middle of this!
I was taking you into
a deep state of relaxation!
I am done with the deep state, okay?
Now, I am in an alert state.
Or else, I'll miss my flight!
You should know that parents
should encourage children,
and their natural talents!
Okay, my little boy!
You did really well! Good job!
I have all my hopes pinned on you!
You'll make me proud!
We'll continue when I am back, okay?
Bye!
Now, let me pack.
You know, Parth lives with his mother.
And Rakhi lives with her father.
Whom would you want to live with?
Mom or Dad?
Well, it doesn't make any
difference to you, does it?
You have a boyfriend!
I am not going too far away.
We'll talk every day, all right?
Hey!
Tell me what's going on, Dad!
You guys are avoiding each other!
And not even talking to each other!
We are not idiots!
And I am not a kid anymore, okay?
That's enough, Dhriti.
You guys fight or not?
So, once in a while, we can also fight.
This is not once in a while.
You guys are going to patch
up before going or no?
Where the hell is my jacket?
Fuck!
Where is my jacket?
Hey!
Come on!
We'll talk on the phone.
Okay?
You both are so selfish!
Don't ever bother calling me!
Come, Dad.
I'll walk you out.
I understand the seriousness, sir.
We are investigating, sir.
God knows what you're doing!
My brother-in-law has
not come home in two days!
-You know who I am, right?
-I know, sir.
What, ma'am?
Do something fast or else, I'll
be forced to talk to your higher-ups.
-I am doing my job, sir. Anything else?
-All right, okay!
-Give me that file.
-What is going on!
-Mr. Kothari, right?
-Yes, ma'am.
How many people work here?
How many women? Men?
I want all the details.
-Okay? I want to meet all of them.
-Sure, ma'am.
Have there been any
complaints against Nanda?
Nothing at all.
From the workers? Especially women?
No, nothing like that.
Is the AC not working?
Welcome to the hot and happening Chennai.
Looks like for a few days,
we'll have to make friends with this heat.
Summer has not even started yet.
Finally,
happy to have you in Chennai, sir.
Nice to meet you, Muthu.
Milind!
Sir?
Great to have you back, man.
Thank you, sir.
Welcome back to you, too!
So, how are you doing, Tiwari?
All good? Missing your corporate job?
I was missing you!
How about a kiss?
Fucker!
How are Suchi and the kids?
Muthu, is there any eatery close by?
I know the right place, I'll take you.
Oh, great! I love South-Indian food!
Which South-Indian food?
There are five states in South India.
Idli.
Sambar.
Menduvada.
Meduvada!
-Chutney.
Who's calling?
Spam.
Name?
My name is Rajalekshmi Sekharan.
-Age?
-32.
How long have you been working here?
A year!
And where were you working before that?
Before this…
I was in my hometown.
My mother was ill,
so I was home for two years.
How is she now?
She passed away.
When was the last time you saw Mr. Nanda?
Tuesday, before I punched out.
He was at his desk.
How is he? Is he a nice guy?
He is a good man, ma'am.
How does he behave with you all?
I had no issues with him.
We only spoke about work.
Did you notice anything
unusual on Tuesday?
Did you see him fight with anyone?
On the phone or in person?
No idea, ma'am.
Write your name and
number in this book, okay?
Next!
Go!
Hello, ma'am.
-Arvind?
-He's there.
Hi, Suchi!
-Hi.
-Welcome back to ShrinkMe.
Glad to see you.
-Beautiful office!
-Thanks.
-Where's Nikhil?
-There he is!
-He's going through some
-Oh, hi!
-beta test results of our new plugins.
-Two minutes!
Come, I'll show you around. Come.
So, Nikhil wanted an open office.
The work is demanding, so he wanted the
atmosphere at work to be light and casual.
And while working over here,
we won't miss our cafes!
Yeah! It does look like a cafe.
Perceptual constancy.
I mean, you gravitate subconsciously
to where you started from.
I've never heard that before.
We've hit one million users. Not bad.
Oh, yes! We have! Come!
This is my workstation, and…
this is for you.
-Thank you.
-And this will be your throne!
Sit!
All the best!
Preparations are underway for
the upcoming bilateral talks…
between the Indian Prime Minister Basu
and the Sri Lankan President,
Lasit Rupatunga.
So, we've set up a temporary
base in this old guest house.
There are a few rooms
upstairs and downstairs.
Talpade, give me the update.
We are tracking down the safe
houses of the informants,
rebel sympathizers and rebels.
We've forwarded a request to have
checkpoints in all of
Chennai's entry points…
airport, railway stations,
and the bus terminuses,
to the headquarters, sir.
Sir, once the local agencies
send us their surveillance data…
I can start facial recognition mapping.
When will the surveillance report come in?
Should be getting it by this evening.
Okay. Look, guys. We aren't just…
tracking the rebels
and their sympathizers.
We are also tracking all
the ISI-backed sleeper cells.
Got it?
Get on with the job!
Punit!
-Punit!
-Yes, sir?
Is the threat analysis report ready?
-When do you need it, sir?
-Well, I needed it yesterday.
If you gave it today,
I would be eternally grateful!
Hey, rascala!
Drink some coffee, be alert,
-and get down to business!
-That's right, JK!
Tamil Nadu means drinking filter coffee
and calling everyone
"yennada rascala," right?
I am just kidding, man!
Relax! Take it easy!
-Thambi!
-Don't call him "Thambi!"
His name is Velu.
Alright, Velu.
Filter coffee?
I am going for a shower.
Calm down, bro!
There's no water supply
here from 8 AM to 8 PM.
Either bathe at night
or early in the morning.
There was a flood here five years ago.
And now, there's no water.
Are you okay?
I am on a break.
After 16 years of married life,
How is the team?
Muthu and his team are smart,
but the information we need…
is not there in any of our systems.
I know a guy.
-Chellam?
-Yes.
He went underground
after the Subbu incident.
He is on ghost mode now.
I've never met a more
paranoid man in my life.
But how will we contact him?
Come, sit.
Brother Selva!
How are you?
Are you both ready for the mission?
We have been waiting for this day.
Also…
Raji will be leading this mission.
Raji?
Is she alive?
Our Chief, Bhaskaran,
has hand-picked each one of us.
There are many assignments
in this mission.
It doesn't matter who leads.
It is critical for us to work as a team.
This is Sajid.
Chief has sent him. Be respectful.
Sajid… this is Karthik.
And this is Prabhu.
Raji!
So good to see you!
You've put on weight!
It'll be gone in a week.
-How are you?
-I am okay.
-Have a seat.
-Come.
Sajid, this is Raji.
The most important part of our plan.
All of you, listen carefully.
Memorize all the details of the plan.
Don't talk to anyone about it. Understood?
And memorize this address.
Tigris Aviation Flying School.
How is everything going, Raji?
I am okay, brother. Getting by.
Any news about your mom?
Yes. Four years back, I got to know that
she was in a refugee camp in Trincomalee.
She killed herself last year.
She was mentally unstable, I heard.
How our people continue to suffer!
I see the shattered face…
of my dead brother every night.
Raji… everything is going
according to plan, right?
I hope you have not raised any suspicions.
-Brother.
-Yes?
Nothing. Never mind.
What's on your mind, Raji? Any problem?
No. Nothing I can't handle.
I hope you are ready
for the mission, Raji.
This is the only reason
I am alive, brother.
Fish, fish, fish!
Come here, sister! Fresh fish, sister!
Will Hindi work here?
Just because you speak Hindi,
doesn't mean the entire world does.
Come, come. Fish, fish, fish!
Hello. One minute.
(speaking broken Tamil)
We are making stingray curry on Sunday.
We'll buy it even if its tail is missing.
(speaking broken Tamil)
We are making stingray curry on Sunday.
We'll buy it even if its tail is missing.
These idiots are talking shit in Hindi!
What?
Hello!
Come here.
-Hello.
-What's up?
(speaking broken Tamil)
-Stingray?
-Stingray! Stingray!
Only the captain of the MV Kamath has it.
I am Srikant Tiwari.
Tell the captain…
meet personally.
Give stingray.
Urgent!
Dhriti, what should I cook today?
Dhriti!
-Dhriti!
-What?
I asked you something, baby.
What should I cook?
I am not hungry, Mom!
Why? Did you eat something
before coming home?
Tell me, what should I cook?
Make whatever you want!
I'll eat it later in my room!
Don't you remember what Dad said?
We have to eat together
as a family, correct?
Then, where is he?
Atharv! Enough of the video games!
Will you stop messaging me?
Isn't it clear that I am not
replying because I don't want to talk?
What the fuck!
You act all lovey-dovey
and then, you start ghosting me!
What is wrong with you?
You didn't even have the decency
to tell me what happened!
Listen!
Things aren't that easy over here, okay?
And…
there are many things in my life that…
I can't do anything about.
I can't help it.
Whatever it is!
Do you know how shitty it is to be treated
like this, and then, you disappear?
Like, how!
See, the thing is,
I already have many problems in my family.
And…
especially my father.
He found out that I am seeing someone.
So, before it became worse, I thought…
I thought… I am not going to talk to you.
He just wants me to focus
on my studies and just…
family business, you know?
So, I am not asking you
to marry me tomorrow!
Idiot!
I don't deserve this!
This is not correct.
Why are you doing this?
Listen, I am sorry.
I know I've made mistakes.
But what I feel for you…
is real.
Trust me on this.
Go to hell!
Excuse me.
"Oh, my forlorn heart, what ails you?
What is the medicine for my blues?
Those, who you expect to be faithful…
don't know what…
-Faith is!
-faith is!"
Well said!
So, you're in the mood for poetry?
Why don't you drink some
water if you're so thirsty?
This is flavored water.
And it's not like I need to go
home, for fuck's sake.
Hey, sad sack!
You guys just had a fight, not a divorce.
Why don't you try talking to her?
What the hell were you thinking?
In your relationship,
do you realize how absent you were
-and how present she was? Think about it.
-Shut up!
This isn't any attendance for a class!
Present, sir! Absent, sir!
Look, Tiwari.
All I know is that the two of you--
Let's not talk about this right now.
Listen to me!
-The two of you--
-Now, don't ruin my evening!
-I am just trying to--
-I am not interested in--
Shut up!
All I know is that both
of you love each other.
And after my parents,
you two are my only family.
And I can't stand
watching my family fight.
Where are the tears, motherfucker!
You don't value me at all.
Give me your phone!
-Give me your phone!
-No! Let it go!
Don't open Suchi's messages.
If she sees a blue tick,
she'll know I've read them.
-Have you changed your password?
-Open it now!
-Tell me your password!
-No! Fucking open it now!
-Show me your face!
-No, no! Open it yourself!
Just show me your damned face!
Who is it?
We've managed to contact him.
Chellam!
It's so fucking hot. I can't sleep.
All good?
JK, what the hell are we doing?
You mean, right now?
Or in life?
How can we say that we're the good guys?
What right do we have to claim
that we save people's lives?
Have you gone mad?
Of course, we're the good guys.
And of course, we have saved many lives.
Why are you lying to yourself?
Remember what happened at Orion?
We failed.
They just twisted the facts
and made up a story.
That it was an accident.
That it was a gas leak.
And the mission was successful.
But our mission was a success.
What about the 48 people who died?
And all those others
who were hospitalized?
-Those lives don't matter?
-Look.
We have saved thousands of lives.
Imagine what would have happened
if the gas leak wasn't stopped.
Yes, we lost the battle.
But we won the war.
Come, let us smoke our blues away.
Sorry, there was traffic, so…
If you'd carried on like
this for another two days…
then I would have said,
"Fuck you" and moved on.
My psycho mode of calls and
messages lasts only a week.
Wow!
This is the first time I've
heard you use the "F-word."
Well, I was fucking hurting!
What did you expect--
Okay, calm down!
Just calm down, okay? Please.
Please, calm down.
See, honestly,
I wasn't going to meet you again.
-See! You never wanted to--
-Just let me speak, please.
The reason being my dad.
He's a very strict person.
He keeps checking my messages, my calls…
all the time.
He even has my email ID and password.
What the hell!
At times, I am just…
I am just scared, but…
Do you like me?
Dhriti!
Yes or no?
Yes, of course, I like you.
Then, we'll figure it out.
If I can smile, so can you!
Yeah, but it's not that easy.
In a couple of years, we'll be adults.
It's our life!
Do you want to come home?
Chief, we have acquired the asset.
We shall take to the skies soon.
Have you activated the eagle?
Yes, Chief.
The eagle is ready for the hunt.
Is Sajid with you?
Yes.
Someone wants to talk to him.
Greetings!
All well?
Yes.
I hope the place and the bird are alright.
Yes, they're just what
we need to achieve our goal.
Which bird are you flying?
The smaller one.
It can fly pretty low.
I've sent you a gift.
Did you receive it?
Yes.
Goodbye.
When are your mom and dad coming back?
This is my uncle's apartment.
I stay beyond Vikhroli, but I come
to stay here every now and then.
Are you boys allergic to staying clean?
Well, I am not.
But I think my uncle is.
Is your uncle Muslim?
No, actually, it's a rented apartment.
Juice?
Yeah.
All boys are the same.
What about this room?
That's my uncle's room.
He keeps it locked when he's not around.
It's really bad.
-Bad?
-Yeah. Taste.
Not a good idea.
Oh, fuck! Fuck!
Shit! I thought my uncle wouldn't
be home until late at night!
-Come on, let's go!
-Chill! What happened?
-Why are you so scared?
-I'll explain later.
-I'll be back in five minutes, stay here!
-What's up, brother?
-I forgot my keys.
-What took you so long?
-I was in the kitchen.
What were you doing there?
Have you seen my keys?
This bag?
Whose is it?
I am asking you a question!
Whose bag is this?
Who the hell have you brought here?
Answer me! Who is it?
-Hi!
-She's my friend.
This is my uncle, Shyam.
Hi… homework…
I had an assignment to do, so…
Anyway, Kalyan, I think it's late.
I should go.
Mom will start calling soon.
Bye.
Are you fucking nuts?
You think you can bring
whoever you want here?
It's not what you think.
This is a part of Sajid's mission.
This is part of his mission!
You fucking piece of shit!
Fucking around is a part of which mission?
I'll talk to Sajid…
and tell him exactly
what the fuck you're up to!
I am sorry! Please! I am so sorry!
What is on the menu?
Idli, dosa, pongal, vada.
One-one plate, each.
-Okay, sir.
-Thank you so much!
You've just ordered for yourself?
-Brother! Two plates, each!
-Okay, sir.
What a wimp, this Chellam!
We've been dying in this
fucking heat for an hour!
No sign of him!
Doesn't value our time!
Fucking idiot!
If something happens to this wimp…
then I won't be able to help you.
Don't turn.
Pick up this newspaper once I leave.
This has the list of the safe
houses used by the rebels.
But we'll need you…
Quite a filmy chap!
-Let's go!
-But--
Pay him, quick!
He hardly ever spoke to us, ma'am,
but he was a nice guy.
-Did he have trouble with someone--
-Ma'am.
She wants to talk to you.
You can go.
Go ahead.
Tell me.
Ma'am, Mr. Nanda really liked Raji.
Raji?
Rajalekshmi, ma'am.
You interviewed her yesterday.
This one.
Why do you say Nanda really likes Raji?
It was pretty obvious, ma'am.
Does Raji know about this?
She is disgusted by it.
But that day, she got into his car.
Okay, thanks. You can go.
Okay, ma'am.
Get that girl.
Looks like she didn't report
for work today, ma'am.
Oh.
-You have her address, right?
-Yes, ma'am.
There! That's 150!
Peanuts! Peanuts!
Who's there?
Is this Rajalekshmi's house?
No.
Have you seen this girl?
Are you sure?
I have lived here for 50 years.
I have never seen this girl.
I want the last known location
of Rajalekshmi's phone.
Now!
Okay, got it.
Head to Adambakkam.
Isn't the last known location
for Nanda's phone also Adambakkam?
Nanda and Raji are up to some shit.
We should lock these shit-heads
up and beat the crap out of them!
What do you mean it'll take two days?
Sri, without judicial permission,
we can't use the local police.
We have a list of the safe
houses used by the rebels!
It is a time-sensitive situation!
And you're explaining to me
about bureaucracy here?
Tiwari!
He hasn't made these rules.
And you're aware of the state machinery.
What can he do?
All this red tapism has fucked our case!
Okay, can we go check
those safe houses ourselves?
This is not advisable, Sri.
All right, let's go!
Go and meet everyone
in the homes listed here.
It's a rebel safe house,
so keep a low profile.
You guys take care of that side.
Check the shop out.
How many corners does this street have?
No idea?
Check in the adjacent street.
-Have you seen this girl?
-No, ma'am. I have never seen her.
-Have you seen her?
-No, ma'am.
That side!
It is locked!
-Look at this photo. Have you seen her?
-No.
-Have you seen her?
-I've seen her.
-Where?
-Over there.
-Which house is it?
-That one, there.
Is there nobody in the next house?
Going somewhere, sweetheart?
Why did you lie to me?
-Do you love him?
-He's a son of a bitch!
Did he do something to you?
If women started speaking out,
all men would be in jail.
And then, nobody would give us jobs.
When did you last see Nanda?
Two days ago.
And then?
He came home, but then left immediately.
Where do you think he will be?
I am not the only one. There are others.
Oh, yeah?
Do you have names?
Isn't it enough to live with this shame?
Now, you expect me to know
about the others too?
Why don't you ask him?
Are you ready to file a complaint?
If you want to file a complaint,
let me know.
I'll take care of the rest.
You lied to me about something else.
What, ma'am?
Your address.
My uncle got me the job,
I don't know what address he gave.
What is this? This chemical smell?
It's from the drainage behind my house.
I've gotten used to it.
The drainage stinks of
all kinds of rubbish, ma'am.
What's in the bag?
Garbage.
Don't leave town without my permission.
Report to the station daily.
Where? Sure, I'll tell her.
Ma'am, they've found a body in Adambakkam.
They want us to check if it's Nanda.
-Where is the body?
-G. H., ma'am.
Go there.
Call Nanda's wife and
ask her to come to G. H.
This way.
Doctor?
This isn't him.
Come, ma'am. Let me get you some water.
What is this smell? I know this smell.
That's formalin.
It's used to prevent
the body from decomposing.
Send a backup unit to Adambakkam!
Ma'am, ma'am! Sorry!
1082. Where?
This? This? Okay. Thank you.
Hands up!
Don't move or I'll kill you!
We are fucked.
What the hell are you looking at?
Murderers! Don't act all innocent!