Krishnamurthy, the forensic team
is on the way. Follow up with them.
Okay, madam.
What are these jokers up to?
They both are jobless fellows, madam.
Madam, listen to me!
Look, my name is Srikant Tiwari.
We are here on an official visit.
Please! We have to make a call!
First, answer my question.
Why did you murder Nanda?
Murder?
-We look like murderers to you?
-Calm down.
-She called us murderers!
-Just shut up! Let me deal with it!
First, let me deal with this.
-What were you doing with the body?
-Nothing!
We didn't do anything… with… with… body!
What we'll do we with the body?
-Removing evidence!
-Evidence? What evidence?
-We didn't know there was a body!
-Just calm down, please!
-But what bo--
-Hey! Calm down!
Madam, madam. No, no.
You are getting us all wrong.
We are government agents, madam.
-Which department?
-TASC!
-Threat Analysis and Surveillance--
-I don't know any TASC!
-Don't tell her all this!
-But--
Because it is a top secret.
Good joke.
Tell this to the magistrate.
Joke? You think this is a joke?
You jokers!
-What are you--
-What did you say?
-Madam!
-I am calling you, "jokers!"
Everybody!
Show them who the jokers are!
-Dude, she's mad!
-Mad?
You're being an idiot! The angrier
you get, the angrier she gets!
"Bhadwa"?
Are you cursing me out in Hindi?
-No, no!
-You want to see what I can do?
This isn't a cussword!
I said if you get angry,
she will get more angry!
"Bhadakegi" is not a cussword!
"Bhadwa" is the cussword, madam!
"Bhadwa" is the cussword.
-What are you doing, man?
-What are they blabbering in Hindi?
Stop screaming at her!
You don't understand women,
that's why you're single! You got it?
As if you're an expert.
-Miss Umiyal!
-Umayal!
Yeah, whatever! I need-- I want phone…
I want to make a call.
It is my right.
Madam, please. We need to make a call.
-We need to.
-Okay. One call!
What is the number?
-Who remembers numbers!
-No, no. I--
It is on my phone.
Please! Please, madam! Please!
Saw how she got it when I
started speaking in legal terms--
-Name?
-Yes, type.
B-H-O-S-D-K.
Calling Sharma?
"Bose DK"?
-Are you kidding me?
-What?
You two think this is a game?
"You two"?
What happened to her now?
Hello? Where is she taking my phone?
No, no, no!
Fucking hell! Motherfucker!
You will spend the night in jail!
Happy now?
If you'd listened to me, we
would have sorted everything out by now.
We're here because
of you in the first place!
Because of me? Are you kidding me!
That's right!
Why couldn't you control her?
-When didn't I try to control her?
-She fucked up my phone!
I still have to pay the EMIs for it
for the next six months!
You really are uncaring and selfish!
Suchi is absolutely right!
-I swear.
-Why are you dragging Suchi into this?
Why shouldn't I?
-Why did you have to bring her up?
-Because she's absolutely right about you!
I'll kill you if you
bring Suchi into this!
-And I will keep quiet!
-Hey! Hey!
-Why are you making so much noise?
-Listen to me, you…
Krishnamurthy,
put that shorty in the other cell!
-Show me what you've got, you little fuck!
-You bet I'll show you, asshole!
-I'll fuck you up!
-I'd like to see you try!
Go to that cell!
-Don't you dare touch me!
-Hey! Get lost!
I'll show you who's the boss!
And you call yourself an officer?
Nonsense!
You don't even believe us
that we are officers!
Shut up!
So, she does speak Hindi!
Then, why the hell was I trying
to talk in English! It was all an act!
You!
What's the payload?
Approximately, 400 kilos.
The takeoff load for
this plane is 500 kilos.
Get rid of all the seats,
except the pilot's seat.
And switch to lightweight tires.
How much does the pilot weigh?
Raji.
Raji, you're early.
Is everything okay?
There was a problem.
The police are looking for me.
What? Police!
Do they know about the mission?
I told you to keep a low profile!
You of all people are
aware of what's at stake!
Were you followed?
No, I wasn't followed, and nobody
knows anything about the mission.
Don't worry, I took care of it.
Okay.
Go, freshen up. Then, we'll talk.
Fuck!
Bloody hell!
What happened?
My back is fucked!
-Try the cobra pose.
-What?
Do yoga now and then.
You've started to look like a constable.
Don't rub salt on my wound.
Just tell me what to do.
Look up at the ceiling.
You okay?
Then, exhale as you come back down.
But from where? My nose or my mouth?
From wherever the hell you can.
Hey! Tea!
-Brother, how about some tea?
-Stop calling him your brother.
They threw us in for a night. All the
big brothers will shove a bamboo up yours.
This guy looks like he's ready for it.
Hey, Muthu is here.
Come on, get up!
-Muthu!
-Andrew, open it!
-Okay, madam.
-One phone call and I can have you fired.
Sorry, sir.
-Open this one, too!
-What the hell were you thinking?
-Sorry, sir. I didn't realize--
-What rubbish!
-Are you out of your mind?
-It's alright.
They told you so many
times, but even then, you--
I said it's alright.
It's just a misunderstanding, right?
But…
you know, madam,
you should have let us call.
I am so sorry, sir.
Do you know, that was a rebel house!
That house… rebel house!
That house belonged to this girl, Raji.
Who?
This girl.
Where have I seen her?
Yeah, I think, I've seen this girl.
JK! Isn't she the one, who we…
-Yes! On the road--
-we met her in that alley!
-Yes! Yes!
-What?
She could be a rebel operative!
Let me cross-check this
with our database, wait.
-Sir!
-Oh, thank you.
My phone!
Put this in rice for 24 hours.
It will work.
Will it really work?
-Fifty percent chance, it might.
-Fifty percent!
I am so sorry, sir.
It's okay. Just call me JK.
Okay, JK Sir.
Just JK.
Shall we?
JK!
Hello? Yes, sir!
You are wasting your time.
That which I sent you,
check and let me know.
-Rice, right?
-Yeah.
Brother, I need to know immediately.
You know,
more than building a features' list,
I think we need to crack
that one everyday problem
this app can solve for the users.
You know, a recent survey
on workplace stress
reveals that the worst
period for corporate workers is…
during the appraisal time.
So, if this app can send a subtle message…
it can help the workers
during this stressful time,
I think that'll be great.
-Alright.
-Yeah?
Can I get a mock-up ready by tomorrow?
Ma'am, there are many changes,
so it'll take some time.
Abdul, I am not asking for details.
It's just a mock-up for the client.
I'll get it done by tomorrow, don't worry.
Thanks, Gunjan.
I think, we should take Abdul
as the test subject for our app.
I really get the feeling that
he's going through some shit.
By the way, how are Atharv and Dhriti?
They're fine. You know, young adults.
And… Srikant?
Has he gotten used to corporate life?
He's in Chennai.
You know, let me work on this.
I'll email it to you.
So… I'll wait for your email.
You can switch on or off
instantly, can't you?
Arvind!
I told you long back that the reason
I joined this company…
was, so that I don't lose my sanity.
And… I'd even said--
Don't take me wrong, Suchi.
You know what? We're friends.
And to act all formal, as colleagues…
We've spent so much time together.
Arvind!
Don't you see?
That's where the problems started!
Suchi, all I want to say is that…
-you don't have to be a stranger.
-What other way is there, Arvind?
You know that chapter
of my life is closed.
I don't want to open that book ever again.
-And if you're expecting that--
-You know what… let it be.
Do your thing.
I am angry with you, Papa!
Why? What's the matter?
You haven't had any time
to call for two days!
You really forgot us!
Are you mad?
I have a really bad network at the hotel.
-You didn't go to school?
-It's a bank holiday today.
What does a bank holiday
have to do with school?
That's just the way things are.
It's complicated.
Okay, listen!
Order me a pizza online, please.
How's Suchi?
She's at work.
-She has already started going to work?
-Yeah, the day after you left.
Really?
She leaves in the morning
and comes back at night.
She works on her laptop
even after she comes back.
I would be willing to give
out more information…
but I would need something in return.
All you'll get is a kick up your bum.
You've become a professional blackmailer!
-You're all alone at home?
-No, Dhriti's here.
-How is she?
-Grumpy, as always.
Let me know about everything
that's happening at home.
Because nobody even
takes my calls anymore.
Don't worry, Sri. I am there, right?
I am your father! Got it?
And listen,
I am ordering that pizza for you.
By the way, Papa! New model is coming!
For what?
The iPhone. Don't you check the news?
Please book it in advance.
Your wish is my command!
Bye! Love you!
Between "I miss you" and "I love you,"
he's made me a jackass.
He's a crook!
He's your son, after all.
Did you talk to Suchi?
No… but she's started going to work.
Oh, nice.
Good for her. She'll be happy.
Yeah, so when have I stopped her?
She used to work before, too.
You think I've ever stopped her?
What sort of a man does that!
-Hey--
-You think I am that kind of a man?
All I am saying is, both of you
sort out your issues, quickly.
Okay, let it go. Forget about it.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Your wife isn't talking to you.
Your daughter won't take your calls.
Your son is blackmailing you!
And you've spent the whole night in jail!
Trying to summarize your
life has depressed me.
Now, people will talk about
my family life in Tamil Nadu, too.
-How?
-You dumbfuck, he understands Hindi!
Muthu is our man.
Do you want to have coffee?
Yeah.
Arvind, I am…
I am really sorry.
I shouldn't have been harsh on
you, I am really sorry.
No, it's okay. It's okay.
It's just that I am…
I am not in a great state lately, and--
Suchi…
I know.
Everything is good.
I should have been more understanding
about how hard this must be for you.
But things will get better.
I promise.
And don't forget to send me those emails.
-Hello, sir.
-Hello.
-Stay away from my phone.
-I am sorry, sir.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
I am really sorry about--
Apologize to him! God knows
what's happening with his phone!
-Is that working?
-At the moment, it's in a coma.
We'll know how it is,
once it regains consciousness.
-Sir.
-Yeah?
I have Nanda's postmortem report.
She killed him with her bare hands.
I think she's a trained fighter.
Okay, thank you.
Sir, I want to be a part
of this investigation.
Tiwari, let her stay.
The decision has been made.
-Thank you--
-Sri!
-Hello, sir.
-Hello.
I want you to see this.
The quality was very poor, sir…
but I used an algorithm.
It compresses the resolution
down so well that--
Damn good! You've done a fantastic job!
Now, show us the image, quickly!
Look.
Raji.
She's a part of the rebels' elite
unit, a commando.
Highly trained in jungle warfare,
hand-to-hand combat…
this unit is responsible
for all the daring missions.
Let's do one thing.
Circulate the photographs of Raji and…
all the rebels in this footage
with our security agencies.
Find out which among
these are still alive.
Yes!
-I pledge my life for the movement.
-I will protect our Tamil race.
-I will give my life for the movement.
-I will--
Come in, Local 52.
Local 52, over.
Three of us are coming on a pilgrimage.
We need to go get the items
for the rituals. Be ready.
We will leave for
Veeraranyam tomorrow morning.
I had a word with Local 52, Jebaraj.
He will make the necessary arrangements.
From here,
we will directly go to Veeraranyam.
First, we will go to this point, then…
Raji!
Sajid, tomorrow morning, the three
of us will leave for Veeraranyam.
From there, we will cross Sri Lanka,
and pick up supplies for the mission.
Raji, I have informed Jebaraj.
He will be waiting for us.
No more screwups!
Prabhu, you and Karthik stay
back and get the plane ready.
From now on,
you all will use these phones.
Only these phones from now on.
Drop your old phones in here.
Hello, Mr. Sambit.
-Are you playing games with us?
-Sorry?
Deepan, I want to know
if you and your comrades
are playing games with my country.
I have no idea what you are talking about!
Deepan, we've been picking up the chatter.
Your preferred channels that have been
lying silent for the past ten years…
have suddenly become a hive of activity.
I don't think this is a coincidence.
See, Bhaskaran has quit our government…
and I am the leader now.
We have nothing to do with what's
going on in Tamil Nadu right now.
Deepan, you need to stop Bhaskaran, now!
Or you will have to pay
the price for his actions.
Mr. Sambit, you know about me.
I believe in dialogue, not violence.
Please, give me some time.
I'll get back to you.
-Sri, JK! Where have you guys been?
-What happened?
The Q branch has intercepted communication
on the radio frequencies
used by the rebels.
The message was cryptic,
and rebel code words were used.
And the language was Sri Lankan Tamil.
Two important words.
One, "Veeraranyam," a code word.
Number two, "Local 52."
Local 52? What's that?
Veeraranyam used to be
the main hub for the rebels.
And maybe, Local 52…
could be a code word
for one of the rebels.
We'll have to find out who.
We should go there.
Sure, but…
we have to be a little careful.
You see, there are a lot
of sympathizers for them.
Before leaving, we should ask
Sri Lankan intelligence agencies…
for information on Raji.
Okay? Because I know,
these people never work alone.
And we should be knowing whom
they are working with here.
Sir, Mr. Deepan is here.
Ask him to come in.
Please come in, Mr. Deepan.
-Come, Deepan.
-Chief, the fish smells divine!
It's your and Subbu's favorite recipe.
Make yourself comfortable.
I still remember this
like it was yesterday.
Even now, sometimes, I make
two cups of coffee by mistake.
Come, let's eat.
Okay.
I have some good news, Chief.
The French Foreign Affairs Minister
has assured us that their government…
is inclined to recognize
our Government in Exile.
Good, good. Glad to see you're busy.
How have you been?
I just lost my brother.
The last member of my family.
How do you think I've been?
Bhaskaran, I don't have to remind you
of the struggle we've had to go through…
to gain some legitimacy for our movement.
Right now, we have to ensure that
we don't make any wrong moves.
Subbu was my brother, as well.
Yes, he was your brother.
And that is why, I trust, you will do
everything you can to bring him justice.
I have retired, Deepan.
The world no longer needs leaders
like me. It needs leaders like you.
Eat!
Mr. Sambit, you are right.
Bhaskaran is up to something.
You guys must watch him carefully.
For everyone's safety,
we will travel separately.
You and Raji take the coastal road.
I'll take the highway.
So, we have classified
it as a platform bug.
We have raised an issue
with the python developer.
Do we have a workaround?
No, but this is not
going to impact the client.
And I am sure by the time we are
ready with the alpha release, we should--
Sorry! Sorry to interrupt, guys…
but I have some really good news!
The client loved the pitch!
Fantastic.
So, congratulations.
Now, they want to see the demo ASAP.
Can we have it ready by next week?
Next week?
I think we'll manage.
Super. So, Arvind and Suchi…
you both might have to go to London
next week to make a presentation.
Be prepared!
And guys, tomorrow is family day.
Don't forget.
-Let's all have fun, okay?
-Yeah.
Carry on, Gunjan. Sorry.
So, let's have a look at the next
bug report in the next slide.
As you can see…
-How much for this?
-18,000.
And how much for this?
28,000.
-How much?
-Twenty-eight thousand only.
-Do you want me to sell my kidney?
-What?
-Something less?
-Show him something cheaper.
Three thousand only.
Okay. Give, give!
Wait, I will pay.
What? No, no! It's okay, Umayal.
No, it was my mistake. I will pay.
It is okay, just forget about the mobile.
But you can buy me a good
filter coffee, please!
-You like coffee?
-I love coffee.
Do you?
No coffee. No tea.
-Copy that!
-You said my name correctly!
-Umayal, right?
-Umayal, yes.
In Marathi also…
You seem to know this route very well.
Have you ever been to Kashmir?
No.
It's very beautiful.
I've heard even Sri Lanka
is extremely beautiful.
Why is so much stuff hidden so far away?
Chennai.
Veeraranyam.
Point Calimere.
Sri Lanka.
Point Pedro, Sri Lanka's northern tip.
One hour by boat.
Veeraranyam was our base.
We used to get all our
supplies from there.
We still have our people there.
-Whom do we have to meet there?
-Jebaraj. He's a smuggler.
He knows the coast guard's
routines and timings.
He's helping us.
We have two hours to reach Veeraranyam.
Talk to the local DSP.
Let's also talk to the local
rebel sympathizers.
Okay.
-Milind!
-Sir!
Keep a plainclothes team on standby.
We need to search all the safe houses.
Talpade!
Send an email to TASC Mumbai
and tell them about our plan.
Email?
Can I do it from your phone?
I don't give my phone to anybody.
Dude, my phone…
I'll have to type each alphabet.
Goddammit, I am working with the buffoons.
Kumar, give me one more drink.
Only after he pays up!
Murugun, I've known you since you were
a child, running around the beach naked.
Relax, I'll repay you.
When Jebaraj gives his word--
Your word means shit!
It has been two months since you paid!
Nobody in this town will entertain you!
Hey, do you realize who
the fuck you are talking to?
-And what are you saying?
-What now?
-How dare you raise your hand on me!
-I am warning you!
Jebaraj!
Jebaraj… are you sure you
will be able to do the job?
Looking at you, I have my doubts.
Chief, you forgot all that I did for you?
Nobody knows the routes as I do.
Don't worry. Everything is set.
We leave tonight and finish the job.
But my money…
You will get your money once
the job is done at Point Pedro.
We'll leave at 9:30 tonight.
Give me a list of the items you need.
Why do you want a list?
Anything that's not on the list is mine.
Also… I need an advance.
For my medicine.
Jebaraj…
don't drink on the job!
Understood?
I had an old list with me.
We've rounded up some
rebel sympathizers from it.
Here they are.
Have you heard from
anyone in the movement?
Oh, no, no.
You guys have no other work, sir?
The whole town of Veeraranyam
used to help the rebels.
They were regulars here…
but it's been many years
since we've seen them around.
Sir, it has been over
11 years since it all ended.
But one thing is sure…
martyrs never die!
Who is Local 52?
Even if someone sneezes, they round us up.
-I hope you know this is harassment!
-Hey!
Please don't hit me, sir!
I really don't know anything!
Who is Local 52?
I don't even remember my name.
What is this 52, 42?
I don't know who is doing
what, but they have my support.
-Pizza.
-Sure.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy.
Sir, your pizza.
Keep it on the table.
Vissa!
Thank you, Visagan.
Take the night off.
Thank you, Chief. Good night.
Indians are watching you.
I have sent you everything
to go underground.
You must leave immediately.
Thank you, Sameer. See you soon.
I'll be in touch.
What trouble are you two cooking up now?
What trouble could I be cooking up!
I am just doing my homework.
I was doing my homework.
Right, very funny.
Tomorrow, it's "bring your
kids to work" day at my office.
So, we're all going, okay?
I am not in the mood to socialize, Mom.
But it'll be fun.
-I don't want to go.
But it's such a small thing,
so what's with all the drama?
Did you go to Dad's office?
No.
Then, why are you forcing me to go?
Fine.
Suchi! Don't worry.
I will come to your office. Okay?
Now, go to bed.
Oh, well!
Sis, why are you always
so angry with Suchi?
Shut up, Atharv!
You don't know shit.
Go to your bed!
Brother.
Between 1:45 a.m. and 2:30 a.m.,
there won't be any coast guard trouble.
So, we can leave for Point Pedro
without setting off any alarms.
And similarly,
we need to be back in Veeraranyam
between 3:45 a.m. and 4:30 a.m.
The three of you, go to Point Pedro,
finish the job, and get back here.
I will wait here and keep watch.
You don't even drink coffee and tea.
Should I call for a lemonade?
Whiskey.
Whiskey!
Sir.
-Cheers.
-Need anything, sir?
-No, thank you.
I'll join you.
This much? Small?
Okay.
Yes.
That's it?
Thanks.
Do you smoke?
-Yes.
-Oh, nice.
Thank you, JK.
JK told me everything…
about what happened in Delhi last year.
I didn't know.
How's your…
-friend?
-Zoya.
She's okay, physically, but…
she saved thousands of
lives, including mine.
I am lucky that I am alive today.
She'd only recently joined TASC.
To Zoya!
This is my hometown
This is my land
Only the sky belongs to all
This is my hometown
This is my land
Only the sky belongs to all
Are you thinking about your homeland?
Rupatunga wants to wipe
out all Sri Lankan Tamils.
Even when she was not
the PM, ten years ago…
Basu was Rupatunga's staunch ally…
and she gave him her
unconditional support.
There was a girl in my unit… Kayal.
She never wanted to leave Eelam.
Along with the others…
she surrendered to the Sri Lankan Army.
But Rupatunga killed her…
and thousands just like her.
Some people were lucky.
They managed to escape.
And the whole world just sat and watched.
I will kill all of them.
I will kill all of them!
Ones who satisfied my hunger
Along with my family
Where to go
Where to go, to live together
Is there any way here?
Hurry up, Jebaraj!
Daybreak is just two hours away.
Fucker, don't order me around!
I don't work for you.
No one is bigger than
the movement, Jebaraj.
Let's finish this and get out of here.
You will never see us again. Move it!
I don't give a shit about
your so-called movement.
I just want everything
that isn't on the list.
That's all!
This is the spot.
You can make yourself useful and dig!
I brought you here, didn't I?
Just because you look serious all the
time, doesn't mean you are some big shit.
Got it?
It's nothing.
I am Jebaraj! King of Veeraranyam!
Stop screaming. The guards will hear us.
The lights haven't come on since evening.
Shit!
He's gone.
(indistinct radio chatter)
Who's there?
I am calling the base.
Alpha two! Alpha two!
Intrusion detected.
(indistinct radio chatter)
Come.
Hey!
What the fuck have you done!
You killed Sri Lankan soldiers!
Fuck this shit! It's none of my business!
I am out of here!
(indistinct radio chatter)
Come in, Unit 65.
Report back, Unit 65!
Unit 65! Report back!