Have you seen this man?
Yes, I have.
Are you sure?
Yes, sir. He lives in that building.
Hello, control room.
Yeah.
Alert all units. I'll be there soon.
-Has anybody visited him?
-Yes, sir.
-What's the update?
-Sir!
He claims that the target
is in block number two.
Mr. Shinde!
Yes, sir.
I'm going to need your help.
Okay, sir.
Syed.
Sir, the water supply will be shut
from 10:00 a.m. to 12:00 p.m. tomorrow.
Please, stock some water
so that there is no trouble.
-Alright.
-Okay? Thank you, sir.
-Was it the watchman?
-Yes.
-Have you seen him before?
-No.
-Yes?
-Sir, it's confirmed.
-There's another guy there, too.
-Who?
Sajid.
Sajid?
Boss! Something's wrong.
-We have to leave.
-Motherfucker!
First, we finish our job.
Then, we leave. Get your stuff.
I can't let the girl live.
Fucking hell!
Take your position.
Block all the exits.
Go! Go! Go! Go! Hurry up!
Let it go!
Come with me!
-We don't have time for this!
-Damn it!
Come on.
Check there!
Dhriti!
-Dad!
-Hey!
Dhriti!
-Dhriti! Open the door!
-Dad!
Don't cry. Dad is here.
Dad is here. Dad is here.
Be strong, okay? Be strong.
-Ajit, take her to the hospital.
-No!
-My child, Uncle Ajit is there.
-No, no, please!
-I'm there. I'm there.
-No, Dad. Please!
-Dhriti!
-Come on! Come on! Come on!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming very soon.
He'll take you safely.
-Did you find them?
-No, sir. We're still looking.
I want him captured! Got it?
Hurry up, guys!
-Come on.
-Yes, sir.
Sir, man down.
Push the target from both sides.
-Bring him towards the center.
-Yes, sir.
-Green team.
-Take positions.
-Yes, sir.
Come on! Move!
Sajid!
You've been surrounded!
Surrender now, and save your life!
There's no way out of this!
Do you understand me?
There's no way out!
Surrender!
Drop your weapon!
Drop it!
Drop the gun! Drop it, Sajid!
He's dead.
Call an ambulance.
Okay, sir.
Hurry up.
We should have captured him alive.
Why? Did you see what he did to Dhriti?
He knew everything about the rebels' plan.
What? You are still
thinking about the mission?
You should be careful at the station.
Check over there, as well.
We're still here,
but the plane is missing.
Anyway, any news about JK?
No, sir. We are still looking for him.
Okay.
Look into my eyes!
There is no pain.
No pain.
No--
No pain?
I want to talk to your
sister, so off you go!
You can call me an "asshole" anytime.
How are you feeling now?
Dad…
I've killed a human being.
You killed a terrorist.
Dhriti.
Kalyan aka Salman… was a terrorist.
He was brainwashed and recruited
to kill innocent people.
Stop feeling guilty. You're very brave.
And he's still alive.
Really?
He's in the government hospital.
He'll be sent to jail
as soon as he recovers.
So, all these years, you
lied about your job?
Dhriti.
He had to lie about his job
because it was a dangerous one.
Both of you were too young
to understand these things.
So, we decided to keep it
a secret till you got older.
I wanted to protect you guys.
I didn't want to endanger your lives.
But I have failed, and I am so sorry.
No, Dad. You didn't.
You are the coolest dad in the world.
Thank you.
What did the doctor say?
After what she's been through,
she needs immediate counseling.
Did he…
I mean, with Dhriti… did he…
did he force himself on her in any way?
-No, no. Not at all.
-Thank God!
-Is he really alive?
-Who?
Whatever his name is… Kalyan… Salman.
He's dead.
Is it really important
for you to go to Chennai?
Can't JK handle things for a few days?
-JK is missing.
-What?
What happened? Is everything okay?
He's just a drama queen. He'll be alright.
I think, he's like a cockroach.
He can survive in any situation.
Come back soon.
Yeah.
Sir, we have found traces of C4.
Judging by the size of the crates,
it would weigh about 200 kilos, sir.
-Thank you, just excuse me.
-Okay, sir.
Yes, Sri.
Muthu, I am coming to Chennai.
I'll be there in roughly three hours.
Any news of JK?
No.
Still searching.
Any leads?
If he's been shot or he's injured…
then by now, there must have
been a lot of blood loss.
Not really sure, Sri.
How's your daughter?
She's… she's fine.
What's the update from forensics?
They have just found traces of C4.
There was a trainer aircraft,
but now it is missing.
I've spoken to the air traffic control,
and they have no record
of any aircraft taking off.
A plane is missing?
They will be searching for the plane.
We will have to get off the highway.
They will be searching the skies.
But you're right.
After we cross the city limits,
we will get off the highway.
Sir, he's here.
I found him.
The address is on the back.
Thank you.
Hello, Mr. Sambit.
He's in Normandy, France.
I'll text you his address.
Silence. We are approaching a checkpoint.
License and RC book, please.
What's there in the vehicle?
Sir! There is nothing at the back.
Just farm equipment, sir. That's it.
Open it up!
No. There's nothing important, sir.
Don't just look at me, open it!
What is this?
It is a windmill, sir.
For our farm.
Where are you headed?
Hosur, sir.
Where is the transit permit?
Sir?
Transit permit!
For transporting industrial
equipment, you need a transit permit!
What are you looking at?
Sir, we are small-time farmers.
Big or small,
rules are the same for everyone!
Come back and collect the truck when
you have a permit! Leave the vehicle!
What are you both blabbering?
No, sir.
Are you teaching me how to do my job?
Grab the keys and park it on the side!
They teach me, it seems!
She seems quite modern.
Is she from Bangalore?
Sir?
Shifting the plane by
road was a clever move.
Good job, Selva.
That was smart thinking on your feet.
Chief, are we going to stop the mission?
No.
We'll never get a chance like this again.
Now, listen to me carefully.
There's a place called Kicha Farms,
about ten kilometers
from Sunguvarsathiram.
Krishnan Ramaswamy owns it.
I've had a word with him.
You can use his farm as a base.
There will be a stretch there.
You can use that as the runway.
He has provided some
men who will help you.
Set up the base quickly,
and finish the job.
Okay, Chief!
Come here!
Tell us where you found this phone!
Sir, I don't know anything.
Let go of me, sir.
I said I don't know.
Put him in the vehicle.
Get in.
Get him out.
Bring him.
Where?
Take him away!
Doctor, come here quickly!
Doctor, check on him.
Muthu!
Sir!
-How is he?
-I am checking.
How is JK?
Come quickly!
-Muthu, man! Let me talk!
-Sri!
Is he alive?
Checking, sir.
Talk to him.
-Easy, easy.
-How bad is he?
What injuries has he sustained?
He was shot in the back.
Doctor, can you feel a pulse?
Give me a minute, I'm checking.
Still checking, sir.
Say something! Say something, goddammit!
There is a pulse, but very weak.
He has a pulse. Get him to the
nearest hospital right away!
And I want hourly updates.
Okay.
They stopped construction
of the highway here…
because they didn't vote for the MLA.
You have about
a 600-meter stretch of land.
Will that be enough, Raji?
Don't have a choice.
We can fly.
-Excuse me, JK Talpade.
-End of the corridor, sir.
Excuse me, doctor.
Hi, I'm Srikant Tiwari.
JK Talpade's friend.
How is he doing? Is he out of danger?
He should be out of the ICU by tomorrow.
Thankfully, the bullet didn't
harm his spinal cord,
and we were able to pull the
bullet out without any difficulty.
Is his family on the way?
We are his family.
-You want to see him?
-Can we?
If you don't mind, just one person.
Just keep it short. He needs to rest.
Sure. I appreciate it, sir.
-Thank you.
We have sent the test to the lab.
We will get it in about an hour.
What are you doing, man?
-Muthu?
-He's outside.
-Dhriti?
-She's okay.
I really felt like
I wasn't going to make it.
I swear!
Motherfucker, the next time
you go on a raid by yourself,
I'll shoot you myself.
Stop crying, asshole.
I'm still alive.
Pushpa!
-I hate tears.
-Motherfucker!
How is Suchi?
Do you really need everyone's
status update right now, fucker?
He needs to relax.
Sorry. I'll be out.
Okay.
Go to sleep.
Get some rest.
Tread carefully with Raji.
Don't worry.
My ass has never been shot, got it?
I'm too smart for that.
Tiwari.
Check this out!
Prabhu, Karthik,
until we finish the mission,
I want the entire perimeter under watch.
And the three of us will take turns
to keep watch through the night.
Okay.
Raji, get some rest.
Tomorrow is your day.
Eat, Raji.
I don't want my soldiers to be weak.
I still remember the day
Chief and I found you.
The same fire still burns in your eyes.
Raji, it is time to make them pay
for all the injustice and
suffering that they gave you.
Yes.
You are my best weapon, Raji.
What you are about to do…
will inspire our cadre
to take up arms again.
You are about to reboot the movement.
I will miss you.
The movement will miss you.
I hope Sajid succeeds in his
mission, as well.
What's the matter?
He didn't make it.
Have they arrested him?
I am a British citizen! You are mistaken!
You are under arrest!
Don't move!
Put your hands behind your back!
You don't have the jurisdiction!
-Stop moving!
-Hey! You bastards!
I'm from the embassy.
We have a warrant for your arrest.
You've got the wrong guy!
-Bastards!
-Cooperate with us!
Bhaskaran!
It's all over.
Your grand plan is going to fail.
France has put their plan to recognize
our government on hold.
All thanks to you and your stupidity.
Where is Raji?
Tell me and make things
easier for everyone.
This is your last chance
to redeem yourself.
France and the UK have agreed
to hand you over to India.
It is all over, Bhaskaran.
So, where is Raji and
what exactly is your plan?
I don't have any plan, Deepan.
Bhaskaran,
I have worked with you for 30 years.
I know you.
Start talking now,
and we can end this amicably.
Or else…
This is how you choose
to repay the sacrifices…
made by our brothers and sisters?
Bhaskaran, please!
I want the same thing as you,
for our homeland to be free.
I am tired of your romance with war.
If you look closely, we aren't different.
There is a difference between you and me.
There is a big difference.
You are a politician.
And I am a soldier.
Martyrs never die.
Hey! Stop him!
Bhaskaran! What have you done?
Stop him! Quick! Stop him!
Bhaskaran!
What are you doing? Stop!
Prime Minister Basu
has arrived in Chennai.
She is on her way to meet…
the Sri Lankan President, Lasit Rupatunga.
With this meeting, Prime Minister Basu…
will flag off her Build India campaign…
by announcing
the Northern Sri Lanka port deal.
We are joined by the senior
business editor, Mr. Vinay Pradhan.
-Welcome to the show, sir.
-Thank you.
So, Mr. Pradhan,
why is this meeting significant?
See, this port deal is
of huge strategic value to India…
as it keeps China out of the Indian Ocean.
It furthers our Prime Minister
Basu's agenda of Build India.
But is she willing to sacrifice
the vote bank of an entire state?
We are doing everything
we can to find this plane.
This is ridiculous!
We can't find a plane?
These rebels are very smart.
Any possibility of them
having gone underground?
Or do you think they are still active?
I am totally convinced
that they are still active.
Otherwise,
why would Bhaskaran kill himself…
rather than reveal their whereabouts?
Anyhow.
You focus on these remaining rebels.
No matter where they are
hiding, you need to find them.
Nothing can go wrong.
Tamilians have never warmed
up to a national party.
And Basu desperately wants to change that.
But this show of camaraderie
with President Rupatunga…
Ma'am, President Rupatunga
has arrived at the airport.
He's on his way to the hotel.
-Sit.
-Thank you.
Would you like some tea?
It's okay, ma'am.
How is Dhriti?
She's feeling much better. Thank you.
JK?
We just got back from the hospital, sir.
We got lucky.
The doctor is saying that
he should recover quickly.
That's very good news, Srikant.
Yesterday, we got to Bhaskaran…
but before we could question
him, he killed himself.
Find that plane, Sri,
and make sure it doesn't take off.
These people are confident that they'll
be able to stop any kind of attack.
But we know that as far as
the rebels are concerned…
we cannot leave anything to chance.
-Do you understand?
-Yes, sir.
Those, who don't care about their own
lives, are certainly more dangerous.
It's a goddamn plane! Not a motorcycle!
How can it go missing?
Sir, my fear is that they
may have dumped the plane…
and now,
they are mobile with that much C4.
Thank you so much, sir. Thank you.
Sri, I think I have some news.
I know what they did to the plane.
What?
They have dismantled it.
I just spoke to a senior
air force officer.
He used to serve in Sri Lanka.
The rebel air force was
created by sourcing planes…
from smaller African countries.
They used to dismantle the planes,
and smuggle them into Sri Lanka, via sea.
In the same way,
they may have dismantled the plane…
and transported it via truck or something!
What are the routes out of Tigris?
Tigris Aviation is on the highway, here.
They probably headed
west, towards Bangalore.
-Okay.
-That's my number one guess.
Another possibility is that they could
have gone north or come down south…
towards Pondicherry.
There's a small chance that
they could have turned around…
to reenter the city, and then
taken some other exit route.
Raise the red alert.
Send your teams to all the checkpoints.
Brief everyone that there may be
a truck carrying a dismantled plane, okay?
Punit! Monitor the situation! As soon as
you have a lead, alert me, ASAP!
Okay? Let's go!
Okay! Both of you! Cover North Chennai!
All the areas near Gummidipundi!
-Yes, sir.
-You cover South Chennai!
-Everything near ECR!
-Yes, sir.
Tell the control room to double
the security at all the exit points!
-No lapses, okay?
-Yes, sir.
-Come on! Double up!
Sir, we are from the TASC Force.
Have you seen this person?
No, sir.
Are you sure?
Sir, daily, lots of vehicles
come to the checkpoint.
How can I remember everyone, sir?
It's a matter of national security, sir.
Sir, I'm also a patriot.
I give my life to my country, sir.
What, sir?
I am also a government
servant like you, sir.
Sorry, sir.
-Muthu.
-Yeah?
Ask everyone around here.
Sir, come here.
Show this photo to all the truckers…
-and ask.
-Cigarette.
Check if they have seen her, got it?
Ask everyone around
here if they've seen her.
What are you looking for, sir?
Muthu.
-What are you looking for, sir?
-No…
there was a truck, and…
we are looking for a truck
and a couple of people.
This one.
Yes, sir. I saw her yesterday.
He claims to have seen her yesterday.
-Get up.
-Sir?
-What happened, sir?
-I want to salute you, sir.
-Stand up! Stand up!
-Sir, you are a patriot, sir.
-Sir, what happened?
-You give your life to the country, sir!
Sir, what?
-You give your life to the country?
-Sir, please! Sir!
-Show me the truck!
-Yes, sir!
-Get me the goddamn truck details!
-Yes, sir.
-Tear it off!
-Yes, sir! Doing it, sir!
Tear it!
Yeah, Punit!
The truck was last
seen at the Bangalore checkpoint.
Any idea where it could
have possibly gone?
Hold on, sir.
Sir, five kilometers down the road,
the highway bifurcates into three forks.
They could have gone in
any of those directions.
There are multiple side roads, as well.
-I'm going to check all of those.
-Keep me posted.
-Fuck! Fuck!
-Alerted all units.
Search operations are on.
I have one more option.
What?
You have broken the protocol.
It is an emergency, sir.
Raji is going to take off with
her plane any minute now, sir.
And they will need an airstrip, sir.
Airstrip? No, Srikant.
The rebel pilots don't need airstrips.
They can take off from any
stretch of road that is long enough.
Sir, their last known location
is the Bangalore excise point.
And their target is
the PM's meeting venue.
Bangalore highway excise checkpoint? Okay.
Is there any open space nearby?
A cricket ground or a football field?
One of Bhaskaran's close friends owned
a property somewhere on that road.
Kicha Farms.
Kicha… Kicha Farms?
Yes, it belongs to Krishnan Ramaswamy.
He used to help Bhaskaran, when they
were fighting for the Tamil cause.
I feel it's our best shot, given
the geography. You could try that place.
Brother Selva!
The plane is ready.
No missing parts?
It's all accounted for, but
we should do a test run.
We cannot.
It is a risk we have to take.
We are heading towards Kicha Farms.
There's a possibility
that the plane is there.
Send a backup team.
We'll be there any minute.
I'll call you as soon
as I have visual confirmation.
Copy.
Madam, the Sri Lankan President
has arrived at the venue.
The meeting should
commence in ten minutes.
I'll be there soon.
Raji, it is time.
You will be flying blind.
I will guide you as best as I can.
You'll take about 12 minutes
to reach the target.
The meeting will last two hours.
Fly low.
I got this, brother.
Martyrs never die.
Karthik!
-They are here!
-Who?
Fast! Get the explosives!
They are here! Take the guns!
Be alert.
Keep looking everywhere.
Be careful, guys.
Yes, sir.
Back off!
Come on! Come on!
Shoot! Shoot!
Cover! Cover!
Raji is getting away! Stop her!
Hey, Muthu!
Muthu, she's heading towards the plane!
Get the car!
Come! Come soon!
Fast! Move!
Get in.
Fast! Fast! Fast!
Fast!
Come on!
Faster, man!
Fast!
Keep the gap.
Keep the gap!
Bring the car near the plane!
Hey, bring it closer!
Get the car! Get the car in the line!
Get the car in the line of the plane!
Come on!
Quick! Get closer!
Shoot it down.
Fast!
Go, go, go! Faster!
Shoot!
Overtake it!
Block the plane! Overtake it!
Stop! Turn the car!
Stop!
This medal is posthumously
awarded to Mr. Milind Hinduja.
Mr. Jayavant Kasinath Talpade.
-Thank you for your service to the nation.
-Thank you, ma'am.
I am honored, ma'am.
Thank you.
Mr. Srikant Tiwari.
I am grateful for what you have done.
If it wasn't for you, I wouldn't be alive.
I will always be thankful to you.
It is my duty, ma'am.
If you ever need anything,
don't hesitate to ask.
Sure.
Thank you, ma'am.
Mr. Punit Banerjee.
Sir, the PM asked if she
could do anything for me.
Shall I talk to her about
an interest-free home loan?
No!
Mr. Muthu Pandian.
Not at all, Srikant.
How much is yours for?
The reward is one lakh.
Same here. After the ten percent
TDS deduction, that's 90,000.
You were so close to becoming
a mini-millionaire.
Sir, medal please.
-We have to return this?
-Yes, sir.
-Please.
-Yeah, alright.
Thank you.
Why do we have to give it back?
You'll get it after your retirement.
Both, the medal and the photo.
Until then, we stay undercover
and so do our medals.
Great.
And then, I was introduced to everyone.
And then, she said, "Mr. Srikant Tiwari…
I am grateful for what you have done.
If it wasn't for you,
I wouldn't be alive."
What is "abhaari"?
Why don't you learn some
Hindi along with English?
It'll come in handy!
"Abhaari" means gratitude, grateful.
Okay.
You know, and then,
she said, "Srikant Tiwari.
Tell me what the country can do for you."
And?
And what?
Not every question has
an answer, my child.
You hear a compliment like
that and feel good about it.
You didn't even take a selfie, Dad.
I just--
-Did you speak to the school principal?
-What?
To discuss when you'll
be going back to school.
Oh, yes. I'll call her tomorrow.
-Very good.
-I know what you're all up to.
You guys were discussing something else,
and when I entered,
you changed the subject.
Nobody changed the subject.
Even at the hospital,
you were speaking in code.
Nobody tells me anything!
I also know that she
didn't have an accident.
It was something else.
I'm not a kid anymore.
He's not a kid anymore!
Okay. Sorry, son.
Please finish your ice cream.
Then, I will hypnotize you!
Hypnosis doesn't work anymore.
Should I try some magic tricks?
Please spare me.
I'm already tired of this hypnosis stuff.
Now, please don't start
a new loop with magic tricks.
At your birthday dinner,
you started a conversation…
but never finished it.
How have you been?
Fine.
Suchi.
What's bothering you?
Sri…
I…
There's something I have
been wanting to tell you.