Jebaraj?
Bringing him back would
have been fatal for the mission.
But the C4 detonators were with him!
It must be at his house.
Let us load up and leave.
Hurry!
This sambar is really good!
Let me tell you!
My wife, Suchi,
makes better sambar than this.
You understand the true value of
homemade sambar only when you step out.
Asshole!
Try this podi.
-I love--
-Idli podi.
Idli podi? How does one eat this?
Put it on your plate.
Make a hole in the middle.
Put some ghee.
And mix it up.
Guys! Please,
don't go out without your weapons.
And make sure you are
never alone when you are out.
How is it possible that an entire region
supports a terrorist organization?
For them, these people aren't terrorists.
They are freedom fighters.
Right!
Across the globe, the role of
terrorists and revolutionaries…
gets redefined from time to time.
The ruling governments
determine the policy.
I can see how these people are
heroes, from their point of view.
If that's how you feel, why
are you hunting them down?
Doesn't matter what I feel.
I just do my duty.
Exactly.
If you shut up and do your
duty, you'll win a medal.
But if you want to express your
opinion, you can go to hell.
Well said, sir.
Srikant, you are late.
-Mr. Chellam--
-Continue washing your hands!
Late for what, sir?
Bhaskaran is trying to find
something for his mission.
If you want to stop him,
you will have to find his team.
But we have no clue who all
are there in Raji's team.
Selvarasan. He was Raji's handler.
If he's on a mission,
he will be there with her.
What have you found out over here?
We have been questioning
all the locals here.
We have managed to get a lead, "Local 52."
Do you know anything about it?
You are questioning the old dogs.
They know nothing.
Local 52 is a smuggler in Veeraranyam.
Jebaraj.
You will find him at this address.
And stop wasting water!
JK!
-Hi, ma'am!
-Hi, Gunjan.
You must be Atharv?
-Hi, I am Gunjan.
-Hello.
-This is for you.
-Thank you.
-Welcome.
-Come.
-Oh! Hi, Suchi!
-Hi!
Hi, Atharv!
So, he works here?
Say hi.
You're looking very smart! Where's Dhriti?
Rhea! Come here!
You remember Auntie Suchi?
Hi, Rhea! How are you?
Do you remember me?
How could she not!
Ever since you made rasam and rice
for her, she's been after my life!
You made rasam and rice for her?
-Yes.
-When?
What does it matter?
-Rhea, this is Brother Atharv--
-Mom, don't bro-zone me.
Hi! I am Atharv.
Mom is coming from America.
Ananya is visiting us from the US.
She wanted to spend some time with Rhea.
That's nice.
You know, I am an expert at hypnosis.
I can hypnotize anyone! Want to try?
-Hi, guys!
-Hi, Nikhil!
-Who is this princess?
-Who is this!
-Hi!
-Hello!
Go, play.
So, this cool dude is your son?
Hi, I am Nikhil.
-Hi, Nikhil. I am Atharv.
-Hey! Address him properly.
-Hi, Uncle Nikhil. I'm Atharv.
-It's all right.
Mom, can I take Rhea?
I want to hypnotize her.
-I'll be with them.
-Come, Rhea!
Thanks.
He's a charmer! Ladies' man!
He's obsessed with hypnosis, nowadays.
Who knows from where
they learn these things!
-Nikhil, I need to ask you something.
-Yes, tell me.
You know the client meeting in London?
Do you really need me there?
Can I skip it?
No, no, no!
Yes, of course, I need you there!
There is no meeting without you, Suchi.
-But--
-Please, make it happen.
Please. You have to go.
-Yeah?
-Okay.
Thank you.
Jebaraj's house is down the lane.
We will wait here. You go inside.
What about his wife?
You know what to do.
Raji!
Noise.
Ask her what they were doing there!
You will have to translate in Tamil.
We are saying this for your own good.
Don't hide it,
just tell us whatever you know.
He left home last night.
He hasn't come back since.
-Did you call him?
-He hasn't called! God knows where he is!
Hey!
Catch her!
Get her quickly!
JK! JK!
JK! Stop her!
Selva! They're all over the place!
Who?
Intelligence!
-We have to cover for Raji!
-Wait!
We have to get this truck out of here!
That is extremely important!
But we can't leave Raji alone.
Sajid, Raji does not need us. Let us go!
Damn it!
-Umayal! Did you see her?
-No!
Follow me! Follow me!
Let's go--
What the hell!
Stop!
Hey, you fool!
Hey, stop!
Stop her!
Stop her! Milind, stop her!
Get her!
-Hey, stop.
-Don't move.
-Hey!
-Raji, stop!
I didn't do anything.
-I didn't do anything.
-Don't move!
It is all because of Nanda.
-Hey, stop acting!
-I did nothing!
Hey!
-Hey, Muthu! What is she saying?
-I did nothing.
-Hey, stop!
-JK, be careful.
-Don't move!
-Stop!
JK, step back! What are you doing?
What the hell is she saying?
No!
JK! Be careful!
Don't do it!
Hey! JK!
-JK! Be careful!
-Raji!
-JK!
-Raji! Don't do this!
-Tiwari!
JK!
Raji!
Don't shoot!
Don't shoot, man! I want her alive!
Go into the lane ahead! Hurry!
-JK! Get up!
-Are you okay?
What? Yes, I'm okay!
Are you okay? Do you need help?
Do you need help?
Die, man!
Hey, catch her!
Put her down!
Don't let her get away!
Hold on to her!
Srikant, there has been an incident
in Sri Lanka at Point Pedro.
Last night, some infiltrators
went there from Veeraranyam.
This used to be an old smuggling route…
and intel suggests that
they smuggled arms.
Sir, I was just about to call you.
This is all a part of
Bhaskaran's plan, sir.
But we may have a breakthrough now.
Raji is in our custody.
Good work, Srikant.
We have to break Raji.
You didn't have to do this, Arvind.
We could have taken an Uber.
It's no big deal.
-Is Dhriti at home?
-She's with her boyfriend!
Atharv! Enough!
She's at home.
You should have brought her along.
I think she would've had fun.
She thinks she's too cool for all this.
-Bye, I'll see you.
-When?
-Tomorrow. At four.
-I will call you.
-Text me!
-I will text you.
Thank you, Arvind.
-What happened?
-Nothing.
Bye!
I need some more.
Bloody hell!
Muthu, please?
Please.
I have called for backup.
They will be here in three hours.
We are only a skeletal
crew at this station.
Madam.
You should all leave before the locals
learn about the rebels' situation.
That's the spot.
You will leave, right?
-Okay, Shekhar.
-Thank you.
Sir, there's a problem--
Understood.
Muthu, you and JK go to Jebaraj's house…
and try to get some
information out of his wife.
Tiwari, can we go after ten minutes?
Muthu, let us go.
Wait! I will go.
Let's talk to Raji.
Yes, sir.
Where are the rest of your friends?
Friend? Where?
I know you aren't working alone.
We also know about Local 52.
Jebaraj? Point Pedro mission?
We know everything about it.
What did you bring back from there?
What is your plan?
You have been lying to me
ever since we met!
Don't you use the rape card!
Shut up and answer his questions!
Raji, we recognize all your friends.
I know you have been brainwashed.
Just tell us about their whereabouts.
Look.
You just have to help us.
Give us their info.
Then, Europe or Canada…
wherever you'd like to relocate…
I will help you with it.
I will arrange everything.
Their chief,
he's hiding somewhere in London.
And he is getting all the dangerous
work done by these young people.
What sort of a leader is he! Your chief!
Don't you dare utter my chief's name!
Just answer the questions! Got it?
If you want to live…
then let me go.
-Stop! Enough!
-She is threatening us, sir!
Enough, enough, enough, Umayal.
This happened eight years ago…
on my wedding anniversary.
My wife…
my daughter…
my little one-year-old son, Vaibhav…
and I… we all went out for dinner.
We were chatting, laughing, and giggling.
Suddenly, a few armed
strangers entered the place.
They looked even younger than you.
They opened fire at people.
Men, women, young, old,
all innocent people…
they didn't spare anyone.
I did whatever I could to try
and get my family out of there.
And then, I started feeling…
the weight in my hands.
I looked down.
It was…
And that day, I decided…
that I will never let
another innocent person die.
I truly believe…
that there is still some
humanity left in you, Raji.
It is there.
And I know it.
My father was a school teacher.
That day, he'd got us new textbooks.
He went to the school to distribute them.
The Lankan Army made
an airstrike on the school…
and my father's dead
body was not even found.
When I was only 15 years old…
the Lankan Army shot down
my brother and his friends.
He was only nine.
After that…
they took me to their base and there…
one after another…
There were so many of them… I lost count.
Then, the Chief…
saved my life.
And my story is real.
Do whatever you want.
Torture me, pour acid over my
body, rape me.
You wouldn't get a word out.
-Bloody dogs!
-Sir, please!
Please, please.
Sir, were you able to get
anything out of her?
Milind, when a man turns into an animal…
he starts behaving worse than them.
And if you mix it with politics…
then, he turns into a monster.
Sometimes, I think,
do we really make a difference?
I am sure we do, sir.
Do we?
At least, I hope so.
Any news?
Jebaraj's wife is worried sick.
He hasn't returned home.
She said that yesterday, he went out
somewhere with three other people.
Raji, some guy from up north,
and the third one was Selvarasan.
She identified him from a photograph.
Did Raji give any information?
She is not going to tell us anything.
Check with people in the nearby villages.
Maybe, someone has seen
Selvarasan or Jebaraj.
We will start with Adhanur?
-Let's go then.
-Okay.
This is going out of control, Sambit!
Major Sameer is hand-in-glove with
Bhaskaran, and Bhaskaran has vanished.
And we have dead Sri Lankan soldiers.
Our agencies are unable to figure out
what was taken from Point Pedro.
And this is because of you!
It's not the time for blame
games, Kulkarni.
Our Prime Minister had a point to prove…
and you have added fuel to the fire.
Now, when that fire has reached
your doorstep, you blame us!
If I start keeping a count
of political fiascoes,
then we will all be in deep shit.
But the difference here is that
whatever I do, I do it for the nation!
Not because I have aspirations
of becoming the Defense Minister!
Our only hope is that…
Srikant gets Raji to talk, soon!
Brother, have you seen Jebaraj?
No?
Brother, have you seen
Jebaraj anywhere around here?
He is a big man.
He doesn't come to shops like ours.
Okay.
Have you seen him around?
No, sir.
Look at him properly.
Hey, that's my house! No one is at home!
Hello, Chief.
-Did anyone follow you?
-No, Chief.
This is an important mission, got it?
Yes, Chief.
Our leader is supervising this.
-When do we start?
-Now.
We have to get going before the
police backup arrives from Trichy.
We were wondering if you've seen
a man named Jebaraj around here.
Check the local bar,
you'll find him there.
Have you seen this man?
No.
Are you sure?
Brother!
You should leave. Your life is in danger.
Sir!
A few local people support rebels, sir.
One MLA's people are spreading lies.
They're saying that
the police killed Jebaraj.
And that there are North Indian
people at the police station, sir.
Yes, I am getting reports
of movement in the village.
Sir, we can't stay here for long.
As soon as the backup comes,
we all leave from here.
Where are they?
-Two hours, sir. There is some delay.
-Two hours!
I will check again, sir.
Sir, let's try to interrogate her!
Let's try to get the truth out of her.
She's a highly trained guerrilla, Milind.
She won't say a thing
without Sodium Pentothal.
We'll have to take her
to Chennai and then see.
Why are they staring at us?
Obviously, we are not welcome here.
Why are people allergic
to us wherever we go!
Just don't make eye contact. Just walk.
Motherfucker! They flattened the tires!
Keep walking.
Milind! Umayal! Call JK and Muthu,
and ask them to return immediately!
Get all the constables inside!
Lock down the entire police station!
Sir, what's happening?
I think, we are under attack.
Don't shoot! Hold the fire!
Don't shoot till I order!
Shekhar! Go down and check!
Sir.
Stay there.
Cover me! Cover me!
Are you okay?
Sir, man down! Sir!
Officer down! Officer down!
Get away from the window!
Step away from the window! Step away!
Fuck!
Go! Get Raji!
Get Raji here!
Hey! Raji!
Untie me if you're a man!
I have no interest in
proving that I am a man!
Move it!
Hey, Sajid! Back off!
Back off!
Put down your weapon!
Put it down!
Or I will kill her!
Get Raji and run!
Hurry up!
Milind?
Oh, shit!
Milind!
Milind! Open your eyes!
Come on! Open them!
Milind!
Open your eyes!
Shit!
Raji, are you okay?
I will live.
The bullet went through.
We will regroup at Tigris in Chennai.
Take care of Raji.
Get to Tigris quickly.
Fuck!
That motherfucker Srikant
is always getting into way!
Make way, make way!
Come!
Make it fast!
Bring from this side.
Come soon, come soon.
Move aside.
Sri?
Sri, where are you?
Sri, what happened?
Nothing, I will call you later.
-Yes, Sajid?
-Greetings, brother.
Greetings. Tell me, what is it?
Raji is back with us!
But there is one problem.
What?
Srikant Tiwari!
That fucking infidel!
He has been a pain in the ass!
Don't worry.
I have a plan…
that will take care of him.
You just give me permission.
And I will take care of him forever.
Activate it, immediately.
Hello?
Salman?
Yes, brother. Greetings.
Greetings.
Do you still talk to that girl?
Dhriti? No. Not at all.
I haven't spoken to her ever
since you asked me to stop.
Brother, he's lying!
He has a romance brewing with her!
Give him the phone!
Try fucking around now!
Talk to him.
-Brother, I--
-Salman!
Do you want to carry out the mission?
Yes or no?
Should I kick you out right now?
Have you forgotten what they
did to your parents?
I haven't.
I will carry out the mission.
I made a mistake. Forgive me.
This is your last chance.
There is a change in plan.
We need that girl in our
possession by tomorrow.
Will you be able to do it?
-Consider it done, brother.
-Now, hang up.